articleId,article,pubDate,ticker,sector,industry,netReturn,links,keywords,topics,entities,reprint,event,relationship,impact,event keyword,found_keywords,keywords_score
de2fa34f6da84e62a9c87ac9a4bc72b2,Marlboro maker Altria agrees to pay $235M to settle Juul-related cases,2023-05-10T23:00:48+00:00,MO,Consumer Defensive,Tobacco,"{'30_days_before': 0.03240076830350602, '5_days_before': -0.01606343220797679, '3_days_before': -0.01651556087222572, '2_days_before': -0.009795283758497142, '1_days_before': -0.015250660311174613, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0041806240247225235, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': -0.015637246542001826, '30_days_after': -0.052233476695729086}","['https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/juul-bought-ads-on-cartoon-network-nickelodeon-to-target-kids-lawsuit-claims/', 'https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2023/05/NYPICHPDPICT000009761792.jpg', 'https://nypost.com/2022/09/06/juul-labs-paying-438-5m-to-settle-states-marketing-probe/', 'https://nypost.com/tag/e-cigarettes/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/04/12/juul-to-pay-462m-to-6-states-over-youth-addiction-claims/', 'https://nypost.com/2020/01/30/altria-takes-a-4-1-billion-hit-on-juul-stake/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/03/22/my-wifes-vaping-habit-killed-her-now-im-warning-others/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/04/17/some-nicotine-free-e-cigarettes-still-have-nicotine-lab-report/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/03/19/schumer-calls-on-fda-to-investigate-elf-bar-hot-new-e-cig/']","[{'name': 'e-cigarette maker Juul Labs', 'weight': 0.09793086}, {'name': 'Juul Labs', 'weight': 0.09615776}, {'name': 'Juul', 'weight': 0.094615474}, {'name': 'Marlboro maker Altria', 'weight': 0.08647481}, {'name': 'local government entities', 'weight': 0.083068945}, {'name': 'local government bodies', 'weight': 0.0808729}, {'name': 'Altria', 'weight': 0.07610238}, {'name': 'Altria Group', 'weight': 0.07601681}, {'name': 'flashy social media campaigns', 'weight': 0.07535793}, {'name': 'individuals', 'weight': 0.06296035}]",[{'name': 'Juul'}],"[{'data': 'Marlboro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Juul', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Juul', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco’s', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sarah London', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Murray Garnick', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
de2fa34f6da84e62a9c87ac9a4bc72b2,Marlboro maker Altria agrees to pay $235M to settle Juul-related cases,2023-05-10T23:00:48+00:00,MO,Consumer Defensive,Tobacco,"{'30_days_before': 0.03240076830350602, '5_days_before': -0.01606343220797679, '3_days_before': -0.01651556087222572, '2_days_before': -0.009795283758497142, '1_days_before': -0.015250660311174613, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0041806240247225235, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': -0.015637246542001826, '30_days_after': -0.052233476695729086}","['https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/juul-bought-ads-on-cartoon-network-nickelodeon-to-target-kids-lawsuit-claims/', 'https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2023/05/NYPICHPDPICT000009761792.jpg', 'https://nypost.com/2022/09/06/juul-labs-paying-438-5m-to-settle-states-marketing-probe/', 'https://nypost.com/tag/e-cigarettes/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/04/12/juul-to-pay-462m-to-6-states-over-youth-addiction-claims/', 'https://nypost.com/2020/01/30/altria-takes-a-4-1-billion-hit-on-juul-stake/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/03/22/my-wifes-vaping-habit-killed-her-now-im-warning-others/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/04/17/some-nicotine-free-e-cigarettes-still-have-nicotine-lab-report/', 'https://nypost.com/2023/03/19/schumer-calls-on-fda-to-investigate-elf-bar-hot-new-e-cig/']","[{'name': 'e-cigarette maker Juul Labs', 'weight': 0.09793086}, {'name': 'Juul Labs', 'weight': 0.09615776}, {'name': 'Juul', 'weight': 0.094615474}, {'name': 'Marlboro maker Altria', 'weight': 0.08647481}, {'name': 'local government entities', 'weight': 0.083068945}, {'name': 'local government bodies', 'weight': 0.0808729}, {'name': 'Altria', 'weight': 0.07610238}, {'name': 'Altria Group', 'weight': 0.07601681}, {'name': 'flashy social media campaigns', 'weight': 0.07535793}, {'name': 'individuals', 'weight': 0.06296035}]",[{'name': 'Juul'}],"[{'data': 'Marlboro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Juul', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Juul', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco’s', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sarah London', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Murray Garnick', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MU,Technology,Semiconductors,"{'30_days_before': -0.11059824357640691, '5_days_before': -0.02916193732612482, '3_days_before': 0.016866385498240377, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006451476334806472, '1_days_after': 0.016287692892603012, '2_days_after': 0.024473687606789918, '5_days_after': 0.022513177272794116, '30_days_after': 0.011935098794091492}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Positive,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,NKE,Consumer Cyclical,Footwear & Accessories,"{'30_days_before': -0.21392077270480292, '5_days_before': -0.15644640443048174, '3_days_before': -0.11301471649513917, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.001546150388958667, '1_days_after': 0.029770772595390405, '2_days_after': 0.02950327645284867, '5_days_after': 0.023206461216692897, '30_days_after': 0.03859515590458529}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Negative,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MO,Consumer Defensive,Tobacco,"{'30_days_before': -0.08259776828687615, '5_days_before': -0.02972357663620906, '3_days_before': -0.0041219536775918275, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0013667475903973436, '1_days_after': 0.011429777843648958, '2_days_after': 0.02377179919116479, '5_days_after': 0.04743264813952608, '30_days_after': 0.07544542735017823}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,META,Communication Services,Internet Content & Information,"{'30_days_before': -0.1536927432665477, '5_days_before': -0.010148335819852194, '3_days_before': 0.00971508914107544, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.004288817640310638, '1_days_after': -0.007249221891417634, '2_days_after': 0.0036168521650388197, '5_days_after': -0.008785199432342905, '30_days_after': -0.3474566604819119}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MU,Technology,Semiconductors,"{'30_days_before': -0.11059824357640691, '5_days_before': -0.02916193732612482, '3_days_before': 0.016866385498240377, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006451476334806472, '1_days_after': 0.016287692892603012, '2_days_after': 0.024473687606789918, '5_days_after': 0.022513177272794116, '30_days_after': 0.011935098794091492}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,NKE,Consumer Cyclical,Footwear & Accessories,"{'30_days_before': -0.21392077270480292, '5_days_before': -0.15644640443048174, '3_days_before': -0.11301471649513917, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.001546150388958667, '1_days_after': 0.029770772595390405, '2_days_after': 0.02950327645284867, '5_days_after': 0.023206461216692897, '30_days_after': 0.03859515590458529}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MO,Consumer Defensive,Tobacco,"{'30_days_before': -0.08259776828687615, '5_days_before': -0.02972357663620906, '3_days_before': -0.0041219536775918275, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0013667475903973436, '1_days_after': 0.011429777843648958, '2_days_after': 0.02377179919116479, '5_days_after': 0.04743264813952608, '30_days_after': 0.07544542735017823}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,META,Communication Services,Internet Content & Information,"{'30_days_before': -0.1536927432665477, '5_days_before': -0.010148335819852194, '3_days_before': 0.00971508914107544, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.004288817640310638, '1_days_after': -0.007249221891417634, '2_days_after': 0.0036168521650388197, '5_days_after': -0.008785199432342905, '30_days_after': -0.3474566604819119}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MU,Technology,Semiconductors,"{'30_days_before': -0.11059824357640691, '5_days_before': -0.02916193732612482, '3_days_before': 0.016866385498240377, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006451476334806472, '1_days_after': 0.016287692892603012, '2_days_after': 0.024473687606789918, '5_days_after': 0.022513177272794116, '30_days_after': 0.011935098794091492}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,NKE,Consumer Cyclical,Footwear & Accessories,"{'30_days_before': -0.21392077270480292, '5_days_before': -0.15644640443048174, '3_days_before': -0.11301471649513917, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.001546150388958667, '1_days_after': 0.029770772595390405, '2_days_after': 0.02950327645284867, '5_days_after': 0.023206461216692897, '30_days_after': 0.03859515590458529}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MO,Consumer Defensive,Tobacco,"{'30_days_before': -0.08259776828687615, '5_days_before': -0.02972357663620906, '3_days_before': -0.0041219536775918275, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0013667475903973436, '1_days_after': 0.011429777843648958, '2_days_after': 0.02377179919116479, '5_days_after': 0.04743264813952608, '30_days_after': 0.07544542735017823}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,META,Communication Services,Internet Content & Information,"{'30_days_before': -0.1536927432665477, '5_days_before': -0.010148335819852194, '3_days_before': 0.00971508914107544, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.004288817640310638, '1_days_after': -0.007249221891417634, '2_days_after': 0.0036168521650388197, '5_days_after': -0.008785199432342905, '30_days_after': -0.3474566604819119}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MU,Technology,Semiconductors,"{'30_days_before': -0.11059824357640691, '5_days_before': -0.02916193732612482, '3_days_before': 0.016866385498240377, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006451476334806472, '1_days_after': 0.016287692892603012, '2_days_after': 0.024473687606789918, '5_days_after': 0.022513177272794116, '30_days_after': 0.011935098794091492}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Positive,Margin/Profitability Discussions,['profitability'],10
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,NKE,Consumer Cyclical,Footwear & Accessories,"{'30_days_before': -0.21392077270480292, '5_days_before': -0.15644640443048174, '3_days_before': -0.11301471649513917, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.001546150388958667, '1_days_after': 0.029770772595390405, '2_days_after': 0.02950327645284867, '5_days_after': 0.023206461216692897, '30_days_after': 0.03859515590458529}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Negative,Margin/Profitability Discussions,['profitability'],10
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,MO,Consumer Defensive,Tobacco,"{'30_days_before': -0.08259776828687615, '5_days_before': -0.02972357663620906, '3_days_before': -0.0041219536775918275, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0013667475903973436, '1_days_after': 0.011429777843648958, '2_days_after': 0.02377179919116479, '5_days_after': 0.04743264813952608, '30_days_after': 0.07544542735017823}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Negative,Margin/Profitability Discussions,['profitability'],10
ec739c40f3f541b28ea7e67b5d531c60,"Nike, Carnival fall; F45 Training, Micron Technology rise",2022-09-30T20:13:30+00:00,META,Communication Services,Internet Content & Information,"{'30_days_before': -0.1536927432665477, '5_days_before': -0.010148335819852194, '3_days_before': 0.00971508914107544, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.004288817640310638, '1_days_after': -0.007249221891417634, '2_days_after': 0.0036168521650388197, '5_days_after': -0.008785199432342905, '30_days_after': -0.3474566604819119}","['https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Norwegian-Cruise-Line-drinks-package-price-hike-17459702.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Walmart-holiday-return-policy-2022-17462152.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/most-romantic-european-trips-for-couples-17446490.php', 'https://www.sfgate.com/shopping/article/Home-Depot-15-Foot-Towering-Phantom-17455677.php']","[{'name': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'weight': 0.13673547}, {'name': 'Micron Technology Inc.', 'weight': 0.12715815}, {'name': 'Nike Inc.', 'weight': 0.119490355}, {'name': 'F45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.10825867}, {'name': 'Amylyx Pharmaceuticals Inc.', 'weight': 0.10689149}, {'name': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.10661197}, {'name': 'analysts', 'weight': 0.096251406}, {'name': 'estimates', 'weight': 0.09148276}, {'name': 'Micron Technology', 'weight': 0.0826591}, {'name': '\n\nF45 Training Holdings Inc.', 'weight': 0.0690569}]",[{'name': 'Nike'}],"[{'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carnival', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'F45 Training', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Micron Technology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rent-A-Center Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Altria Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Juul Labs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lou Gehrig’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,Margin/Profitability Discussions,['profitability'],10
cb1569aed6a346c7acbab85a96d16e5f,Farmers Worry $8.2 Billion Agriculture Deal Will Diminish Competition,2023-06-17T14:07:00+00:00,BG,Consumer Defensive,Farm Products,[],"['https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-04-05-2023?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/news/markets?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/regulators-accuse-pesticide-makers-of-inflating-prices-for-farmers-11664549061?mod=article_inline', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/chicken-companies-agree-to-pay-85-million-to-settle-antitrust-allegations-11658781469?mod=article_inline', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/bunge-viterra-to-merge-to-create-global-agribusiness-giant-ffdf44e0?mod=article_inline', 'https://www.wsj.com/market-data?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-stock-market-is-on-sale-that-doesnt-make-it-cheap-11658388069?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-03-31-2023?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/ADM']","[{'name': 'chicken farmers', 'weight': 0.08070245}, {'name': 'Farmers', 'weight': 0.07968246}, {'name': 'farmers', 'weight': 0.07968246}, {'name': 'grain markets', 'weight': 0.07865927}, {'name': 'higher consumer prices', 'weight': 0.07659368}, {'name': 'higher food prices', 'weight': 0.07521956}, {'name': 'global commodity trading', 'weight': 0.07373642}, {'name': 'companies', 'weight': 0.06721386}, {'name': 'market dynamics', 'weight': 0.06386402}, {'name': 'international markets', 'weight': 0.061453052}]",[],"[{'data': 'Bunge', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 13}, {'data': 'Glencore', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Viterra', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Cargill', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Farm Action', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Archer Daniels Midland', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Louis Dreyfus', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Agriculture Department', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'the Consumer Federation of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'National Corn Growers Association', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'the American Antitrust Institute', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wayne-Sanderson Farms', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Federal Trade Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'JPMorgan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Maxwell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Greg Heckman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Thomas Gremillion', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chuck Grassley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Diana Moss', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Canada', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Iowa', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Argentina', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Brazil', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'R.', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'State of the Union', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South America', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Causal,Negative,Mergers and Acquisitions,"['acquisition', 'merger', 'consolidation', 'deal making']",29
cb1569aed6a346c7acbab85a96d16e5f,Farmers Worry $8.2 Billion Agriculture Deal Will Diminish Competition,2023-06-17T14:07:00+00:00,BG,Consumer Defensive,Farm Products,[],"['https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-04-05-2023?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/news/markets?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/regulators-accuse-pesticide-makers-of-inflating-prices-for-farmers-11664549061?mod=article_inline', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/chicken-companies-agree-to-pay-85-million-to-settle-antitrust-allegations-11658781469?mod=article_inline', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/bunge-viterra-to-merge-to-create-global-agribusiness-giant-ffdf44e0?mod=article_inline', 'https://www.wsj.com/market-data?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-stock-market-is-on-sale-that-doesnt-make-it-cheap-11658388069?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-03-31-2023?mod=series_marketslive', 'https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/ADM']","[{'name': 'chicken farmers', 'weight': 0.08070245}, {'name': 'Farmers', 'weight': 0.07968246}, {'name': 'farmers', 'weight': 0.07968246}, {'name': 'grain markets', 'weight': 0.07865927}, {'name': 'higher consumer prices', 'weight': 0.07659368}, {'name': 'higher food prices', 'weight': 0.07521956}, {'name': 'global commodity trading', 'weight': 0.07373642}, {'name': 'companies', 'weight': 0.06721386}, {'name': 'market dynamics', 'weight': 0.06386402}, {'name': 'international markets', 'weight': 0.061453052}]",[],"[{'data': 'Bunge', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 13}, {'data': 'Glencore', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Viterra', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Cargill', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Farm Action', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Archer Daniels Midland', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Louis Dreyfus', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Agriculture Department', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'the Consumer Federation of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'National Corn Growers Association', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'the American Antitrust Institute', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wayne-Sanderson Farms', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Federal Trade Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'JPMorgan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Maxwell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Greg Heckman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Thomas Gremillion', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chuck Grassley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Diana Moss', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Canada', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Iowa', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Argentina', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Brazil', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'R.', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'State of the Union', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South America', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Industry Competitiveness,Causal,Negative,Industry Competitiveness,['market share'],9
e7774cfc673948daad5a5d733fd85b88,Stock futures little changed after the S&P 500’s best week since March,2023-06-04T22:03:14+00:00,CPB,Consumer Defensive,Packaged Foods,"{'30_days_before': -0.05973698977440889, '5_days_before': 0.027947045486140687, '3_days_before': 0.001655021199060025, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.0037523718151103447, '1_days_after': -0.0853360538621768, '2_days_after': -0.077862096905154, '5_days_after': -0.09324496239492686, '30_days_after': -0.1128583444466742}","['https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/bank-of-america-magnificent-seven-stocks-driving-2023-market-gains.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/jobs-report-may-2023-.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/next-questions-for-markets-center-on-skinny-rally-and-fed-derailment.html']","[{'name': 'last week', 'weight': 0.08509963}, {'name': 'week', 'weight': 0.078640826}, {'name': 'chief investment officer', 'weight': 0.06380763}, {'name': 'labor market strength', 'weight': 0.06357331}, {'name': 'chief investment strategist', 'weight': 0.0633556}, {'name': 'S&P Global', 'weight': 0.060742117}, {'name': 'strong jobs data', 'weight': 0.06005419}, {'name': 'Frost Investment Advisors', 'weight': 0.059873465}, {'name': 'Stock futures', 'weight': 0.05871726}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.054868877}]","[{'name': 'S&P'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Labor Department', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Frost Investment Advisors', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BMO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'J.M. Smucker', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Campbell Soup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'United Natural Foods', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stitch Fix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Signet Jewelers', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'DocuSign', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'S&P Global', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'hourly earnings', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mace McCain', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yung-Yu Ma', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
e7774cfc673948daad5a5d733fd85b88,Stock futures little changed after the S&P 500’s best week since March,2023-06-04T22:03:14+00:00,SPGI,Financial Services,Financial Data & Stock Exchanges,"{'30_days_before': 0.06435103852204294, '5_days_before': 0.03822235813989139, '3_days_before': 0.004544721242146554, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.007508476426631883, '1_days_after': -0.00934801402257568, '2_days_after': 0.005505968087331947, '5_days_after': 0.009207914107690174, '30_days_after': 0.012852078768437636}","['https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/bank-of-america-magnificent-seven-stocks-driving-2023-market-gains.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/jobs-report-may-2023-.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/next-questions-for-markets-center-on-skinny-rally-and-fed-derailment.html']","[{'name': 'last week', 'weight': 0.08509963}, {'name': 'week', 'weight': 0.078640826}, {'name': 'chief investment officer', 'weight': 0.06380763}, {'name': 'labor market strength', 'weight': 0.06357331}, {'name': 'chief investment strategist', 'weight': 0.0633556}, {'name': 'S&P Global', 'weight': 0.060742117}, {'name': 'strong jobs data', 'weight': 0.06005419}, {'name': 'Frost Investment Advisors', 'weight': 0.059873465}, {'name': 'Stock futures', 'weight': 0.05871726}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.054868877}]","[{'name': 'S&P'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Labor Department', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Frost Investment Advisors', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BMO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'J.M. Smucker', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Campbell Soup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'United Natural Foods', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stitch Fix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Signet Jewelers', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'DocuSign', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'S&P Global', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'hourly earnings', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mace McCain', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yung-Yu Ma', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Positive,,[],0
e7774cfc673948daad5a5d733fd85b88,Stock futures little changed after the S&P 500’s best week since March,2023-06-04T22:03:14+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.03808530179081937, '5_days_before': 0.04873495218392898, '3_days_before': 0.03873096922493158, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0001278500104199276, '1_days_after': 0.028151172900121813, '2_days_after': 0.001259778334422812, '5_days_after': -0.019666595681583465, '30_days_after': -0.026396191426264703}","['https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/bank-of-america-magnificent-seven-stocks-driving-2023-market-gains.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/jobs-report-may-2023-.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/02/next-questions-for-markets-center-on-skinny-rally-and-fed-derailment.html']","[{'name': 'last week', 'weight': 0.08509963}, {'name': 'week', 'weight': 0.078640826}, {'name': 'chief investment officer', 'weight': 0.06380763}, {'name': 'labor market strength', 'weight': 0.06357331}, {'name': 'chief investment strategist', 'weight': 0.0633556}, {'name': 'S&P Global', 'weight': 0.060742117}, {'name': 'strong jobs data', 'weight': 0.06005419}, {'name': 'Frost Investment Advisors', 'weight': 0.059873465}, {'name': 'Stock futures', 'weight': 0.05871726}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.054868877}]","[{'name': 'S&P'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Labor Department', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Frost Investment Advisors', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BMO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'J.M. Smucker', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Campbell Soup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'United Natural Foods', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stitch Fix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Signet Jewelers', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'DocuSign', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'S&P Global', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'hourly earnings', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mace McCain', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yung-Yu Ma', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
932236803dd24721af5483ab40901f6e,"I talked to 1,000 CEOs of highly successful companies—and they all agree this is the No. 1 type of employee",2022-10-18T15:35:47+00:00,CPB,Consumer Defensive,Packaged Foods,"{'30_days_before': 0.056783438353406046, '5_days_before': -0.0072247012614909956, '3_days_before': -0.0071471778422276255, '2_days_before': -0.0071471778422276255, '1_days_before': -0.03362723014439872, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0006296280944015908, '1_days_after': -0.01362623095212201, '2_days_after': -0.02990459673077006, '5_days_after': -0.03510633938096064, '30_days_after': -0.06174018206422471}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/27/4-main-paths-to-becoming-millionaire-here-is-the-easiest-way-says-money-expert.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/23/self-made-millionaire-simple-money-habits-i-used-to-save-1-million-and-retire-early-at-35.html', 'https://institute.theceoforumgroup.com/radio-directory', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/23/author-who-studied-millionaires-says-do-not-play-the-loterry-if-you-want-to-retire-rich.html', 'https://theceoforumgroup.com/', 'https://theceoforumgroup.com/radio/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/make-it-newsletters/']","[{'name': 'employee', 'weight': 0.087603025}, {'name': 'CEO', 'weight': 0.06880402}, {'name': 'CEOs', 'weight': 0.06880402}, {'name': 'Air Defense Artillery', 'weight': 0.068672314}, {'name': 'Prudential Group Insurance', 'weight': 0.064738385}, {'name': 'West Point', 'weight': 0.06211457}, {'name': 'different projects', 'weight': 0.061797917}, {'name': 'different backgrounds', 'weight': 0.059823573}, {'name': 'Americas leading financial services companies', 'weight': 0.0595936}, {'name': 'other industries', 'weight': 0.05880487}]",[{'name': 'Business Leaders'}],"[{'data': 'the ""The CEO Show""', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Proctor & Gamble', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Dunkin' Brands"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LinkedIn', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ryder System', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Fireman's Fund Insurance Company"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Prudential Group Insurance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Whole Foods', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MTV International', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'West Point', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Air Defense Artillery', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'USAA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Robert Sanchez', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Lori Fouche', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'John Mackey', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bill Roedy', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Robles', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Doug Conant', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
2b8f7a64b263468396f549c70249ac4f,I'm a shopping expert and Amazon's fluffy Presto toilet paper is the only one I buy,2023-03-03T21:20:10+00:00,CLX,Consumer Defensive,Household & Personal Products,"{'30_days_before': 0.006848942136979286, '5_days_before': 0.0072342156668480095, '3_days_before': -0.020301631946427645, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0250727071879574, '1_days_after': -0.005760423352063282, '2_days_after': 0.0005436155559294109, '5_days_after': 0.019844503238448663, '30_days_after': 0.009019286720945319}","['https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B0B51W3FBD&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=SEAAES%2B51%2BInch%2BIce%2BScraper%2Band%2BSnow%2BBrush%2Bwith%2BSqueegee%2C%2BExtendable%2BSnow%2BIce%2BRemoval%2Bwith%2BFoam%2BGrip%2Bfor%2BWindshield%2BSUV%2BTruck%2BVehicle%2BWindow&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B0B51W3FBD&brand=SEAAES&price=35.98&salePrice=13.98&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9TRUFBRVMtU2NyYXBlci1TcXVlZWdlZS1FeHRlbmRhYmxlLVdpbmRzaGllbGQvZHAvQjBCNTFXM0ZCRC8_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAXVDGUHkL0Vmj2QlxvdF6hBjricGDJaTJi6pWQGLAU97', 'https://www.amazon.com/amazonprime?&linkCode=ll2&tag=stock-up-and-save-oct5-20&linkId=4e3b1ba96c96ebe4cfeed3810cdc38b0&language=en_US&ref_=as_li_ss_tl', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B079WWFZY6&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=4-in-1%2BKitchen%2BKnife%2BAccessories%3A%2B3-Stage%2BKnife%2BSharpener%2BHelps%2BRepair%2C%2BRestore%2C%2BPolish%2BBlades%2Band%2BCut-Resistant%2BGlove%2B%28Black%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B079WWFZY6&brand=KITCHELLENCE&price=30.0&salePrice=11.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9wcm9kdWN0L0IwNzlXV0ZaWTY_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAZmAhEJaGoEmCxZDj8UkK03GF_SmzoLOEHHcl5kv55OE', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1IxN01HS0EzNUFTUjRNLz90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1ei0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAAfBfSpymnr3Jc4jyv6FX2QdRc7wuzjDVQN-rGiDKg-4q&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FR17MGKA35ASR4M%2F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07HF3X6Y4&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Hilife%2BSteamer%2Bfor%2BClothes%2C%2BPortable%2BHandheld%2BDesign%2C%2B240ml%2BBig%2BCapacity%2C%2B700W%2C%2BStrong%2BPenetrating%2BSteam%2C%2BRemoves%2BWrinkle%2C%2Bfor%2BHome%2C%2BOffice%2Band%2BTravel&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07HF3X6Y4&brand=Hilife&price=38.99&salePrice=23.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9IaWxpZmUtU3RlYW1lci1IYW5kaGVsZC1DbG90aGluZy1DYXBhY2l0eS9kcC9CMDdIRjNYNlk0P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAdu9mJNrjIuAh5pNgfOLhQ64qyvWKgeZP_0rRIjcrL-_', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1IyODI3VzFPRlYzTkw2P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAZXbx927fUAi1w-M5whBrgN6kRzL0sUTy_db_t7qG34k&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FR2827W1OFV3NL6%3F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDlDRDZaN0dCP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAUz6uZ0ql7JRFN0PrYcXtsrtx3Ud69MBSnW7S-8NazsH&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09CD6Z7GB%3F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B073WFLD35&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Utopia%2BKitchen%2BNonstick%2BFrying%2BPan%2BSet%2B-%2B3%2BPiece%2BInduction%2BBottom%2B-%2B8%2BInches%2C%2B9.5%2BInches%2Band%2B11%2BInches%2B%28Grey-Black%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B073WFLD35&brand=Utopia+Kitchen&price=43.99&salePrice=29.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9VdG9waWEtS2l0Y2hlbi1Ob25zdGljay1GcnlpbmctUGFuL2RwL0IwNzNXRkxEMzU_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAcem7wT2Jj75QsakyKDFdXisweRaKI7Y1LjjW1g8lTnT', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B08P2T2NXH&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=OKP%2BLife%2BK2%2BRobot%2BVacuum%2BCleaner%2B1800%2BmAh%2C%2BBlue&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B08P2T2NXH&brand=OKP&price=399.99&salePrice=138.88&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9wcm9kdWN0L0IwOFAyVDJOWEg_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAWRab3IIJbfC57bSOGvRJNGYlyahTzBG4cNT0wRFeRX_', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B072Q31PBF&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Samsonite%2BWinfield%2B2%2BHardside%2BExpandable%2BLuggage%2Bwith%2BSpinner%2BWheels%2C%2BChecked-Large%2B28-Inch%2C%2BBrushed%2BAnthracite&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B072Q31PBF&brand=Samsonite&price=309.99&salePrice=218.7&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9TYW1zb25pdGUtV2luZmllbGQtSGFyZHNpZGUtRXhwYW5kYWJsZS1MdWdnYWdlL2RwL0IwNzJRMzFQQkY_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAX3NqeCtIajBU6BaeBKny6dzjp0ba2uVI2ZQfmWRs92i', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07MQRZPSG&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=COZSINOOR%2BBed%2BPillows%2Bfor%2BSleeping%2B%5BPack%2Bof%2B2%5D%2BHotel%2BQuality%2BPillows%2BPremium%2BPlush%2BFiber%2C%2BBreathable%2BCooling%2BCover%2BSkin-Friendly%2Bfor%2BSide%2BBack%2Band%2BStomach%2BSleepers%2B%28Queen%2BSize%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07MQRZPSG&brand=COZSINOOR&price=89.99&salePrice=29.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9wcm9kdWN0L0IwN01RUlpQU0c_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAARfyrGdVe5B5aEarm7yVPTsQvZgmYyr-Fro1HAM8Mku1', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B085D4MFS8&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=iRobot%2BRoomba%2B692%2BRobot%2BVacuum-Wi-Fi%2BConnectivity%2C%2BPersonalized%2BCleaning%2BRecommendations%2C%2BWorks%2Bwith%2BAlexa%2C%2BGood%2Bfor%2BPet%2BHair%2C%2BCarpets%2C%2BHard%2BFloors%2C%2BSelf-Charging%2C%2BCharcoal%2BGrey&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B085D4MFS8&brand=iRobot&price=299.99&salePrice=189.0&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9pUm9ib3QtVmFjdXVtLVdpLUZpLUNvbm5lY3Rpdml0eS1TZWxmLUNoYXJnaW5nLUNoYXJjb2FsL2RwL0IwODVENE1GUzg_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAARW42xS8jrHxdgZXxykJO8PkmN-_Vph_56oWoL7j439w', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1IzMkZIVUJKQTFWNUUwLz90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1ei0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAAboKzO6vNz8IBLJujkgF1lV5BFiJ1_AbaNfGnIS5co1G&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FR32FHUBJA1V5E0%2F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B004WULC3I&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=T-fal%2BNonstick%2BDishwasher%2BSafe%2BCookware%2BLid%2BFry%2BPan%2C%2B10-Inch%2C%2BBlack&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B004WULC3I&brand=T-fal&price=54.99&salePrice=29.89&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ULWZhbC1VbHRpbWF0ZS1Bbm9kaXplZC1Ob25zdGljay1EaXNod2FzaGVyL2RwL0IwMDRXVUxDM0k_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAdU3UAQyVjkmuBBqH4j13OW3ccApp-7TS8GausB2DROe', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07GW9TJ3G&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=ColorCoral%2BCleaning%2BGel%2BUniversal%2BDust%2BCleaner%2Bfor%2BPC%2BKeyboard%2BCleaning%2BCar%2BDetailing%2BLaptop%2BDusting%2BHome%2Band%2BOffice%2BElectronics%2BCleaning%2BKit%2BComputer%2BDust%2BRemover%2Bfrom%2B160G&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07GW9TJ3G&brand=ColorCoral&price=11.99&salePrice=5.94&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9LZXlib2FyZC1Vbml2ZXJzYWwtS2V5Ym9hcmRzLUNhbGN1bGF0b3JzLUNvbG9yQ29yYWwvZHAvQjA3R1c5VEozRy9yZWY9c3JfMV8xX3NzcGE_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAUSWWZdOyWxN9yJ9aWZs9Cs4WGd7gAcPBfAOS9HHpqHw', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07TPRTV6P&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Joyoldelf%2BSock%2BDrawer%2BOrganizer%2BDivider%2B2%2BPacks%2BUnderwear%2BOrganizer%2C%2B24%2BCell%2BCollapsible%2BCloset%2BCabinet%2BOrganizer%2BUnderwear%2BStorage%2BBoxes%2Bfor%2BStoring%2BSocks%2C%2BHandkerchiefs%2C%2BTies%2C%2BBelts%2B%28Grey%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07TPRTV6P&brand=Joyoldelf&price=14.99&salePrice=9.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9Kb3lvbGRlbGYtT3JnYW5pemVyLVVuZGVyd2Vhci1Db2xsYXBzaWJsZS1IYW5ka2VyY2hpZWZzL2RwL0IwN1RQUlRWNlA_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAeCWCYxcKVKcKJNE6rg-fdk1jFmg9vmRlEDP7XFK70yP', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B092ZDHJMN&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Fab%2Btotes%2B6%2BPack%2BClothes%2BStorage%2C%2BFoldable%2BBlanket%2BStorage%2BBags%2C%2BStorage%2BContainers%2Bfor%2BOrganizing%2BBedroom%2C%2BCloset%2C%2BClothing%2C%2BComforter%2C%2BOrganization%2Band%2BStorage%2Bwith%2BLids%2Band%2BHandle%2C%2BGrey&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B092ZDHJMN&brand=Fab+totes&price=41.99&salePrice=29.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9GYWItdG90ZXMtQ29udGFpbmVycy1Pcmdhbml6aW5nLU9yZ2FuaXphdGlvbi9kcC9CMDkyWkRISk1OP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAARApmnk7ROe2GGXRNX_CV9d2ZlXUpsKAgRE5bntADIA4', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B09F9KWSXJ&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=SpaceAid%2BBag%2BStorage%2BOrganizer%2Bfor%2BKitchen%2BDrawer%2C%2BBamboo%2BOrganizer%2C%2BCompatible%2Bwith%2BGallon%2C%2BQuart%2C%2BSandwich%2Band%2BSnack%2BVariety%2BSize%2BBag%2B%284%2BPack%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B09F9KWSXJ&brand=SpaceAid&price=28.88&salePrice=22.0&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDlGOUtXU1hKP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAZGxUAB36tPdcCaW1X8_ZtkNZfM0Y9fmJH3AykL0u0kE', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B08TN2GC94&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=iRobot%2BBraava%2Bjet%2Bm6%2B%286012%29%2BUltimate%2BRobot%2BMop-%2BWi-Fi%2BConnected%2C%2BPrecision%2BJet%2BSpray%2C%2BSmart%2BMapping%2C%2BWorks%2Bwith%2BAlexa%2C%2BIdeal%2Bfor%2BMultiple%2BRooms%2C%2BRecharges%2Band%2BResumes%2C%2BBlack&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B08TN2GC94&brand=iRobot&price=499.99&salePrice=314.0&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9pUm9ib3QtQ29ubmVjdGVkLVByZWNpc2lvbi1Db21wYXRpYmxlLVJlY2hhcmdlcy9kcC9CMDhUTjJHQzk0P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAflMOQyJIh8mPRgBg0JTMnNgKeyKeMyPUb0ki4gs1XsN', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07L9KDSNN&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=OSULLOC%2BPremium%2BTea%2BCollection%2BGift%2BSet%2C%2BPremium%2BOrganic%2BPure%2B%26amp%3B%2BBlended%2BTea%2Bfrom%2BJeju%2C%2BTea%2BBag%2BSeries%2B40%2Bcount%2C%2B8%2Bflavors%2Bx%2B5%2BEA&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07L9KDSNN&brand=Osulloc&price=39.99&salePrice=25.0&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9Pc3VsbG9jLVByZW1pdW1UZWEtQ29sbGVjdGlvbi00MC1Db3VudC9kcC9CMDdMOUtEU05OP3JlZl89T2N0X0RMYW5kaW5nU19EXzY1YjY0YmRiXzYwJnRhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAWxEVHy-5shtcVIteVLSggi9zzoX81q2pKRkPgunRVLc', 'https://www.amazon.com/WAG-Freeze-Chicken-Breast-Treats/dp/B08H66NKQN?', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B00JH98GR4&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Shark%2BNV360%2BNavigator%2BLift-Away%2BDeluxe%2BUpright%2BVacuum%2Bwith%2BLarge%2BDust%2BCup%2BCapacity%2C%2BHEPA%2BFilter%2C%2BSwivel%2BSteering%2C%2BUpholstery%2BTool%2B%26amp%3B%2BCrevice%2BTool%2C%2BBlue&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B00JH98GR4&brand=Shark&price=219.99&salePrice=159.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9TaGFyay1OYXZpZ2F0b3ItUHJvZmVzc2lvbmFsLUFudGktQWxsZXJneS1OVjM2MC9kcC9CMDBKSDk4R1I0P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAARzO8FjxRBIvE5IlEOQwLrtj-Gqq6z1j3h0onfaBIjCY', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B00006JSUA&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Lodge%2BL8SK3%2B10-1%2F4-Inch%2BPre-Seasoned%2BSkillet&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B00006JSUA&brand=Lodge&price=34.25&salePrice=19.9&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDAwMDZKU1VBP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAeDsbXqd7VPL40fayoTqejHHdOs3OTWdtYo9V1pzJPWx', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07VGRVKSN&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=HOTOR%2BCar%2BTrash%2BCan%2Bwith%2BLid%2Band%2BStorage%2BPockets%2C%2B100%25%2BLeak-Proof%2BCar%2BOrganizer%2C%2BWaterproof%2BCar%2BGarbage%2BCan%2C%2BMultipurpose%2BTrash%2BBin%2Bfor%2BCar%2B-%2BBlack&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07VGRVKSN&brand=HOTOR&price=24.99&salePrice=9.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9IT1RPUi1MZWFrLVByb29mLU9yZ2FuaXplci1XYXRlcnByb29mLU11bHRpcHVycG9zZS9kcC9CMDdWR1JWS1NOLz90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1eC0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAAW2Bu6wpOQqTWQmULeY4LjOZt2UA4c3AYfSbx2YZoktF', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B00P21TAIK&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Chill%2BSack%2BBean%2BBag%2BChair%3A%2BGiant%2BMemory%2BFoam%2BFurniture%2BBags%2Band%2BLarge%2BLounger%2C%2BBig%2BSofa%2Bwith%2BHuge%2BWater%2BResistant%2BSoft%2BMicro%2BSuede%2BCover%2C%2BCharcoal%2C%2B5-feet%2B%28AMZ-5SK-MS03%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B00P21TAIK&brand=Chill+Sack&price=149.99&salePrice=127.49&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9DaGlsbC1TYWNrLUJlYW4tQmFnLUNoYWlyL2RwL0IwMFAyMVRBSUs_cmVmXz1PY3RfRExhbmRpbmdTX0RfYTZiM2EyNjlfNjQmdGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAASsEEXb4WjclNmy3zel91d6PLl4fORTu1XnQGU_mvgNV', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9BbWF6b24tQnJhbmQtUHJlc3RvLTMwOC1TaGVldC1VbHRyYS1Tb2Z0L2RwL0IwNzRDUks1NFgvP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAaMQrR59WbmxqX6MrMIykNWO1KrkLdhttuoy9mwXQMDO&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAmazon-Brand-Presto-308-Sheet-Ultra-Soft%2Fdp%2FB074CRK54X%2F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07S76WBGF&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Ninja%2BAG301%2BFoodi%2B5-in-1%2BIndoor%2BGrill%2Bwith%2BAir%2BFry%2C%2BRoast%2C%2BBake%2B%26amp%3B%2BDehydrate%2C%2BBlack%2FSilver&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07S76WBGF&brand=Ninja&price=229.99&salePrice=149.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9OaW5qYS1EZWh5ZHJhdGUtSW5kb29yLUVsZWN0cmljLUFHMzAxL2RwL0IwN1M3NldCR0Y_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAARLnDCCrQMWdL8kwyQRWrR7OkvJuVlHBouENarAsVG-O', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07ZWRZBMG&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=T-fal%2C%2BUltimate%2BHard%2BAnodized%2C%2BNonstick%2B14%2Bin.%2BWok%2C%2BBlack%2C%2BE76589%2C%2B14%2BInch&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07ZWRZBMG&brand=T-fal&price=59.99&salePrice=38.3&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ULWZhbC1VbHRpbWF0ZS1Bbm9kaXplZC1Ob25zdGljay1FNzY1ODkvZHAvQjA3WldSWkJNRz90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1eC0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAAWrqEbQctYN0fNZN8AH9DW9rtHAhJGBSknNOTJRAxRk4', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B079FK5QKD&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=UTTU%2BSandwich%2BPillow%2BQueen%2BSize%2C%2BOrthopedic%2BPillow%2Bfor%2BNeck%2BPain%2BRelief%2C%2BCervical%2BPillow%2Bfor%2BBack%2BPain%2C%2BNeck%2BSupport%2Bfor%2BSide%2BSleepers%2C%2BAdjustable%2BMemory%2BFoam%2BPillow%2C%2BCertiPUR-US&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B079FK5QKD&brand=UTTU&price=59.99&salePrice=44.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9wcm9kdWN0L0IwNzlGSzVRS0Q_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAASuoDSQVybXycjobIG-tVs-gZYFzyNe8rophVhhPMd7K', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B08NWJD654&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Casper%2BSleep%2BPillow%2Bfor%2BSleeping%2C%2BStandard%2B%28Pack%2Bof%2B2%29%2C%2BWhite%2B2%2BCount&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B08NWJD654&brand=Casper&price=119.0&salePrice=101.96&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9DYXNwZXItU2xlZXAtUGlsbG93LVNsZWVwaW5nLVN0YW5kYXJkL2RwL0IwOE5XSkQ2NTQvcmVmPXNyXzFfMl9zc3BhP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAdsiuuJ3k8LYCpZr4XVdjNygRGynyW3Hc6zMAfbJ4GiK', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07BNS7T6V&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Signature%2BDesign%2Bby%2BAshley%2BChime%2B12%2BInch%2BPlush%2BHybrid%2BMattress%2C%2BCertiPUR-US%2BCertified%2BFoam%2C%2BQueen&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07BNS7T6V&brand=Signature+Design+by+Ashley&price=478.08&salePrice=289.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9Bc2hsZXktRnVybml0dXJlLVNpZ25hdHVyZS1EZXNpZ24tSW5uZXJzcHJpbmcvZHAvQjA3Qk5TN1Q2Vi9yZWY9c3JfMV84P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAW4MYrocqGz3dFWD7z8L1DtoAI4rvNY5GRshxNbg41WJ', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B0716M151K&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=LuxClub%2B6%2BPC%2BSheet%2BSet%2BSheets%2BDeep%2BPockets%2B18%22%2BEco%2BFriendly%2BWrinkle%2BFree%2BSheets%2BMachine%2BWashable%2BHotel%2BBedding%2BSilky%2BSoft%2B-%2BCream%2BKing&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B0716M151K&brand=LuxClub&price=61.99&salePrice=37.95&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9MdXhDbHViLUZyaWVuZGx5LUh5cG9hbGxlcmdlbmljLUFudGktQmFjdGVyaWEtV2FzaGFibGUvZHAvQjA3MTZNMTUxSy8_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAX61OWjDJsBAy8kAQ1BoBqN9r_Ux7rlbwd_70rlFjUKh', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1IyUzFLWUkwOVFYUTUzP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAARMbrSK0ubZ3dZiFVC0uUwiMZXvX_uG_vFULVonRyXrR&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FR2S1KYI09QXQ53%3F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07Y8BXBX8&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=GABRYLLY%2BErgonomic%2BMesh%2BOffice%2BChair%2C%2BHigh%2BBack%2BDesk%2BChair%2B-%2BAdjustable%2BHeadrest%2Bwith%2BFlip-Up%2BArms%2C%2BTilt%2BFunction%2C%2BLumbar%2BSupport%2Band%2BPU%2BWheels%2C%2BSwivel%2BComputer%2BTask%2BChair&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07Y8BXBX8&brand=GABRYLLY&price=329.5&salePrice=215.6&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9HYWJyeWxseS1Fcmdvbm9taWMtTWVzaC1PZmZpY2UtQ2hhaXIvZHAvQjA3WThCWEJYOD90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1eC0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAARTnBSRXI6_leqlh8N-8O_aqVyYSxbLzSe7BpwNDbmXG', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9RLXRpcHMtQ290dG9uLVN3YWJzLTUwMC1wYWNrL2RwL0IwMDAwNTMwNEg_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXotMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAASyRYn1nX0xKgaZQSb4vQMT-nSbtXZxDXKpL6dxtQ2XI&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FQ-tips-Cotton-Swabs-500-pack%2Fdp%2FB00005304H%3F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B074CRK54X&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Amazon%2BBrand%2B-%2BPresto%21%2B313-Sheet%2BMega%2BRoll%2BToilet%2BPaper%2C%2BUltra-Soft%2C%2B6%2BCount%2B%28Pack%2Bof%2B4%29%2C%2B24%2BFamily%2BMega%2BRolls%2B%3D%2B120%2Bregular%2Brolls&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B074CRK54X&brand=Presto%21&price=28.84&salePrice=28.84&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9BbWF6b24tQnJhbmQtUHJlc3RvLTMwOC1TaGVldC1VbHRyYS1Tb2Z0L2RwL0IwNzRDUks1NFgvP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAY0GCDGrG9eFTvdRp1cwg1oOUxSPoHf0urH0648o0WVI', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B09498GV6R&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&providerId=amazon&featureId=product-url&itemName=Amazon%2BBasics%2BCotton%2BSwabs%2C%2B500ct%2C%2BPack%2Bof%2B4%2B%28Previously%2BSolimo%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B09498GV6R&brand=Amazon+Basics&price=11.5&salePrice=11.5&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9BbWF6b24tQmFzaWNzLUNvdHRvbi1QcmV2aW91c2x5LVNvbGltby9kcC9CMDk0OThHVjZSP3RoPTEmdGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAZmjYuLVQxF_WV_7FnV_2cJWKnJWu35CeIao0NmeHL_H', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B0BMDH6YQC&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=BISSELL%2B3277%2BCrossWave%2BX7%2BCordless%2BPet%2BPro%2BTitanium%2FBlack%2FCopper%2BVacuum&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B0BMDH6YQC&brand=Bissell&price=499.99&salePrice=383.0&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9CSVNTRUxMLUNyb3NzV2F2ZS1Db3JkbGVzcy1UaXRhbml1bS1Db3BwZXIvZHAvQjBCTURINllRQz90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1eC0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAAV5G9jcOKyxusNE7sHyK8FpeUgIwqSf7dBLh3KYCyi42', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07M7S1G95&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Molblly%2BQueen%2BMattress%2C%2B10%2Binch%2BGel%2BMemory%2BFoam%2BMattress%2Bwith%2BCertiPUR-US%2BBed%2BMattress%2Bin%2Ba%2BBox%2Bfor%2BSleep%2BCooler%2B%26amp%3B%2BPressure%2BRelief%2C%2BQueen&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07M7S1G95&brand=Molblly&price=409.99&salePrice=229.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9NYXR0cmVzcy1Nb2xibGx5LUNlcnRpUFVSLVVTLUNlcnRpZmllZC1QcmVzc3VyZS9kcC9CMDdNN1MxRzk1P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAWnKprnonH6K-nk3FaWWpylPFf2O0aBp9VcRI8a-KHdq', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B09TT9L1Q9&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=SOLEJAZZ%2B2-Tier%2BUnder%2BSink%2BOrganizer%2C%2BSliding%2BUnder%2BBathroom%2BCabinet%2BStorage%2BDrawer%2BOrganizer%2Bwith%2BHooks%2C%2BHanging%2BCup%2C%2BDividers%2C%2BHandles%2C%2BMulti-purpose%2BUnder%2BSink%2BShelf%2BOrganizer%2C%2BBlack%2C%2B2%2BPack&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B09TT9L1Q9&brand=SOLEJAZZ&price=49.99&salePrice=39.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9TT0xFSkFaWi1Pcmdhbml6ZXItQmF0aHJvb20tRGl2aWRlcnMtTXVsdGktcHVycG9zZS9kcC9CMDlUVDlMMVE5P3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAWNpFLpWSwYzAJZyR8SLb8h2PX4mIUDKWZNh71ay6C4d', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07Q3DWSTX&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=RENPHO%2BAir%2BPurifiers%2Bfor%2BBedroom%2C%2BHEPA%2BFilter%2BAir%2BPurifiers%2Bwith%2B22dB%2BQuiet%2B4%2BSpeed%2BControl%2Bfor%2BAllergies%2C%2BPets%2C%2BSmoke%2C%2BDust%2C%2BPollen%2C%2BSmall%2BAir%2BCleaner%2Bfor%2BHome%2BOffice%2BLiving%2BRoom%2BKitchen%2C%2BWhite&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07Q3DWSTX&brand=RENPHO&price=59.99&salePrice=47.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9SRU5QSE8tQWxsZXJnaWVzLVB1cmlmaWVycy1FbGltaW5hdGVzLUFsbGVyZ2Vucy9kcC9CMDdRM0RXU1RYP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAdp7TA3m8MTBWv-khevIgF0hSqH7ABeuqq2uKFuIw82W', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B09YZ33MTL&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Instant%2BEssentials%2B4QT%2BAir%2BFryer%2BOven%2C%2BFrom%2Bthe%2BMakers%2Bof%2BInstant%2BPot%2Bwith%2BEvenCrisp%2BTechnology%2C%2BNonstick%2Band%2BDishwasher-Safe%2BBasket%2C%2BFast%2BCooking%2C%2BEasy-to-Use%2C%2BIncludes%2BFree%2BApp%2Bwith%2Bover%2B100%2BRecipes&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B09YZ33MTL&brand=Instant+Pot&price=79.95&salePrice=54.95&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9JbnN0YW50LUVzc2VudGlhbHMtUG90LVRlY2hub2xvZ3ktRGlzaHdhc2hlci1TYWZlL2RwL0IwOVlaMzNNVEw_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAATJW5FLC2kYJbgcmXTJavr3mfXqpEMNmR4IgqIl20_MD', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B01DIMTWCS&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=FORTEM%2BCar%2BTrunk%2BOrganizer%2C%2BCar%2BStorage%2BOrganizer%2C%2BCollapsible%2BMulti%2BCompartment%2BCar%2BOrganizer%2C%2BSUV%2BTrunk%2BOrganizer%2C%2BNon%2BSlip%2BBottom%2C%2BAdjustable%2BSecuring%2BStraps%2C%2BFoldable%2BCover%2B%28Black%2C%2BStandard%2BSize%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B01DIMTWCS&brand=FORTEM&price=34.99&salePrice=24.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9GT1JURU0tT3JnYW5pemVyLUNvbGxhcHNpYmxlLVNlY3VyaW5nLUluY2x1ZGVkL2RwL0IwMURJTVRXQ1MvcmVmPXNyXzFfNj90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1eC0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAAScFVWUnLMTssvsHNjbdRJJefEchL-RgM294r5VZglNj', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B004QM8SLG&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Lodge%2BSeasoned%2BCast%2BIron%2B5%2BPiece%2BBundle.%2B10.5%22%2BGriddle%2C%2B8%22%2BSkillet%2C%2B10.25%22%2BSkillet%2C%2B10.25%22%2BDutch%2BOven%2C%2Band%2B10.25%22%2BLid&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B004QM8SLG&brand=Lodge&price=150.0&salePrice=89.9&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9Mb2RnZS1TZWFzb25lZC1CdW5kbGUtR3JpZGRsZS1Ta2lsbGV0L2RwL0IwMDRRTThTTEc_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAARA53KWqI0XeoDzh9fWRJWjzGOXJSPgtXTSmtttp8XRt', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9BbWF6b24tQnJhbmQtSGFwcHktQmVsbHktQ2hvY29sYXRlL2RwL0IwNzFHQjVIOUM_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXotMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAaMZLJrMvqHjFGd2j1_fQQ4m_fx2wQ5MfTpAZW4jw5wY&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAmazon-Brand-Happy-Belly-Chocolate%2Fdp%2FB071GB5H9C%3F', 'https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08WQB5WVP?', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B00H2RJE4M&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=Sleep%2BInnovations%2BMarley%2B10%2BInch%2BCooling%2BGel%2BMemory%2BFoam%2BMattress%2Bwith%2BAirflow%2BChannel%2BFoam%2Bfor%2BBreathability%2C%2BKing%2BSize%2C%2BBed%2Bin%2Ba%2BBox%2C%2BMedium%2BFirm%2BSupport&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B00H2RJE4M&brand=Sleep+Innovations&price=399.99&salePrice=295.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9TbGVlcC1Jbm5vdmF0aW9ucy0xMC1pbmNoLU1hdHRyZXNzLVdhcnJhbnR5L2RwL0IwMEgyUkpFNE0_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAaCA5QPQT_yEE5u8GHJ9eL4E2COjR7C5IuLss3APOXEh', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1IyUTZZQUo3VVBLOFFSP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAASNegbitmniZT_kJJBvQLSHq2v0H_q4aYBzzdYbGHt0Z&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FR2Q6YAJ7UPK8QR%3F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07F24HVRR&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&providerId=amazon&featureId=product-url&itemName=Amazon%2BBasics%2BDisinfecting%2BWipes%2C%2BLemon%2BScent%2C%2BSanitizes%2FCleans%2FDisinfects%2FDeodorizes%2C%2B85%2BCount%3A%2BPack%2Bof%2B3%2B%28Previously%2BSolimo%29&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07F24HVRR&brand=Amazon+Basics&price=9.29&salePrice=9.29&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDdGMjRIVlJSP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV4LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAX3cTV8etsjd62NPYaeavwX8GsiA1wWeQ5Eqyjky9yZO', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B0BFHR6LHZ&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=whall%2BCordless%2BVacuum%2BCleaner%2C%2B25kPa%2BSuction%2B4%2Bin%2B1%2BFoldable%2BCordless%2BStick%2BVacuum%2BCleaner%2C280W%2BBrushless%2BMotor%2B55%2BMins%2BRuntime%2CLightweight%2BHandheld%2BVacuum%2Bfor%2BHome%2BHard%2BFloor%2BCarpet%2BPet%2BHair&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B0BFHR6LHZ&brand=whall&price=499.99&salePrice=127.49&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS93aGFsbC1Db3JkbGVzcy1WYWN1dW0tQ2xlYW5lci1MaWdodHdlaWdodC9kcC9CMEJGSFI2TEhaL3JlZj1zcl8xXzQ_dGFnPXlsZTAxLXAtby00dXgtMjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImMwZjM3ZmNlLWU4OTctMzcyOS1iMmIxLWVkYzY3MGU5MGIzZiJ9&signature=AQAAAZjELkr4dzFBXjktkwHVwdbB1lfx-4oOaq49UeUwLYCo', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1JVVDJHWTkzTFVIRUgvP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAexvdrxIHF66H6hTJxEOCuE0Rzf86higmAp8OOOm2imw&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FRUT2GY93LUHEH%2F', 'https://www.amazon.com/dp/B093X8QQ12?', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9ncC9jdXN0b21lci1yZXZpZXdzL1IzN1ZOVVpIUks3OTJCP3RhZz15bGUwMS1wLW8tNHV6LTIwIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiJjMGYzN2ZjZS1lODk3LTM3MjktYjJiMS1lZGM2NzBlOTBiM2YifQ&signature=AQAAAU8-elsZAHibZylZhrcyWh1Y-8l0AIDqSDEbhw951b1Y&gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fcustomer-reviews%2FR37VNUZHRK792B%3F', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&itemId=amazon_B07S8GF4LV&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=pnr-product-module&featureId=product-url&itemName=TAILI%2BHanging%2BVacuum%2BStorage%2BBags%2BSpace%2BSaver%2BBags%2Bfor%2BClothes%2C%2B4%2BPacks%2BLong%2B53x27.6%2Binches%2C%2BVacuum%2BSeal%2BStorage%2BBag%2BClothing%2BBags%2Bfor%2BSuits%2C%2BDress%2BCoats%2Bor%2BJackets%2C%2BCloset%2BOrganizer%2Band%2BStorage&merchantName=Amazon&itemSourceId=B07S8GF4LV&brand=TAILI&price=33.99&salePrice=29.99&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9UQUlMSS1IYW5naW5nLVN0b3JhZ2UtQ2xvdGhpbmctT3JnYW5pemVyL2RwL0IwN1M4R0Y0TFYvcmVmPXNyXzFfND90YWc9eWxlMDEtcC1vLTR1eC0yMCIsImNvbnRlbnRVdWlkIjoiYzBmMzdmY2UtZTg5Ny0zNzI5LWIyYjEtZWRjNjcwZTkwYjNmIn0&signature=AQAAATrePW72oi6ppw3PvY2UNll7wJ7UtZgd__S6CYO6j6IK', 'https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&siteId=us-lifestyle&pageId=1p-autolink&featureId=text-link&merchantName=Amazon&custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkw