articleId,article,pubDate,ticker,sector,industry,netReturn,links,keywords,topics,entities,reprint,event,relationship,impact,event keyword,found_keywords,keywords_score
66f56cf369ce48ab86c22a782f6ad391,"Aflac, Ing, PRI, Unum: Life Insurance Stocks Hit New 52-Week Highs",2023-08-06T21:52:54+00:00,AFL,Financial Services,Insurance - Life,"{'30_days_before': 0.09723002516618928, '5_days_before': 0.07957227674410494, '3_days_before': 0.0027041340902249633, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.005289519148674149, '1_days_after': -0.010999113323636234, '2_days_after': -0.010729124197015882, '5_days_after': -6.37520396454816e-05, '30_days_after': -0.015056940932732243}","['http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidkudla/2023/08/04/catching-up-with-catch-up-contributions/', 'https://www.multpl.com/shiller-pe', 'https://www.forbes.com/companies/wells-fargo', 'https://www.forbes.com/companies/unum', 'https://www.forbes.com/companies/aflac', 'https://news.primerica.com/forbes-names-primerica-one-of-americas-best-insurance-companies-for-2022/', 'https://www.forbes.com/lists/best-employers-women/?sh=6c6fcad1466c', 'https://www.forbes.com/companies/primerica']","[{'name': 'Life Insurance Stocks', 'weight': 0.09372203}, {'name': 'life insurance', 'weight': 0.08976342}, {'name': 'best insurance companies', 'weight': 0.08322728}, {'name': 'insurance products', 'weight': 0.082406744}, {'name': 'Price', 'weight': 0.07802163}, {'name': 'price', 'weight': 0.07802163}, {'name': 'unexciting value stocks', 'weight': 0.06276857}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.06125289}, {'name': 'Shareholder equity', 'weight': 0.058505308}, {'name': 'shareholder equity', 'weight': 0.058505308}]","[{'name': 'Insurance'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Aflac', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ing', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'PRI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Unum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'American Family Life Assurance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley Bank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Forbes', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Wells Fargo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Columbus', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Georgia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'the United States', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netherlands', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Australia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Duluth', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ireland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'England', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Poland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Latin America', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asia', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Positive,,[],0
e4eb022f0c2e4851969f31f347ebc20f,Madonna announces 2023 tour that will celebrate her greatest hits,2023-01-17T17:52:05.294000+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': 0.06357281736977205, '5_days_before': -0.01154922835556893, '3_days_before': -0.012904412830817336, '2_days_before': -0.012904412830817336, '1_days_before': -0.010873921641812112, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.006095786123373692, '1_days_after': 0.013427317693382568, '2_days_after': 0.013427317693382568, '5_days_after': 0.02745498677972935, '30_days_after': 0.16112540049804358}","['https://www.instagram.com/p/CnhNliDBfP5/?hl=en', 'https://www.madonna.com/news/title/madonna-announces-the-celebration-tour', 'https://ticketmaster.ca/americanexpress', 'https://www.madonna.com/tour']","[{'name': 'local time', 'weight': 0.108408384}, {'name': 'Jan.', 'weight': 0.10801195}, {'name': 'other famous European cities', 'weight': 0.07924634}, {'name': 'other major cities', 'weight': 0.076302096}, {'name': '2 p.m. local time', 'weight': 0.0722543}, {'name': '6 p.m. local time', 'weight': 0.0722543}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.06815551}, {'name': 'hits', 'weight': 0.0678817}, {'name': '10 a.m. local time', 'weight': 0.065674394}, {'name': '9 a.m. local time', 'weight': 0.065674394}]","[{'name': 'Music'}, {'name': 'Madonna'}]","[{'data': 'Madonna', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Amy Schumer', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Jack Black', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lil Wayne', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Judd Apatow', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Caldwell Tidicue', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bob the Drag Queen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madonna: The Celebration Tour', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Truth or Dare', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Instagram', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Citi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Canada American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Ticketmaster', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'European American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'four-minute', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10 a.m. local time', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 15}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Vancouver', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Seattle', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Denver', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chicago', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Paris', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Milan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Berlin', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Toronto', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Montreal', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sweden', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'France', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Italy', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netherlands', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Spain', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Belgium', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'North American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 3}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
fc344a9de43b49bcaf00acb53c81e7b9,Investors warn ‘fluffy’ ESG metrics are being gamed to boost bonuses,2023-08-27T11:00:08+00:00,LUV,Industrials,Airlines,"{'30_days_before': -0.07359047835244936, '5_days_before': -0.0199337526007215, '3_days_before': -0.006717966037625089, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.010428607276395385, '1_days_after': -0.0094918086839344, '2_days_after': -0.008831824562430146, '5_days_after': -0.016293592684636482, '30_days_after': -0.09535632845103914}","['https://www.ft.com/cms/s/25aed60d-1deb-4a41-8f39-00c92702b663,s01=1.html?ftcamp=traffic/partner/feed_headline/us_yahoo/auddev']","[{'name': 'top executives', 'weight': 0.13340631}, {'name': 'bonuses', 'weight': 0.11462318}, {'name': 'data', 'weight': 0.103368565}, {'name': 'payouts', 'weight': 0.0997584}, {'name': 'companies', 'weight': 0.09880704}, {'name': 'an ESG data analytics firm', 'weight': 0.09797688}, {'name': 'Investors', 'weight': 0.095005736}, {'name': 'investors', 'weight': 0.095005736}, {'name': 'Southwest Airlines', 'weight': 0.08857699}, {'name': 'Esgauge', 'weight': 0.08141351}]",[],"[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Conference Board', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Esgauge', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Southwest Airlines', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
fc344a9de43b49bcaf00acb53c81e7b9,Investors warn ‘fluffy’ ESG metrics are being gamed to boost bonuses,2023-08-27T11:00:08+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': -0.04297865056877004, '5_days_before': -0.01582228036567057, '3_days_before': -0.003358774195967751, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0007695936640164103, '1_days_after': -0.004270172827878005, '2_days_after': -0.01627153953701288, '5_days_after': -0.007902583168164279, '30_days_after': -0.01846127428012123}","['https://www.ft.com/cms/s/25aed60d-1deb-4a41-8f39-00c92702b663,s01=1.html?ftcamp=traffic/partner/feed_headline/us_yahoo/auddev']","[{'name': 'top executives', 'weight': 0.13340631}, {'name': 'bonuses', 'weight': 0.11462318}, {'name': 'data', 'weight': 0.103368565}, {'name': 'payouts', 'weight': 0.0997584}, {'name': 'companies', 'weight': 0.09880704}, {'name': 'an ESG data analytics firm', 'weight': 0.09797688}, {'name': 'Investors', 'weight': 0.095005736}, {'name': 'investors', 'weight': 0.095005736}, {'name': 'Southwest Airlines', 'weight': 0.08857699}, {'name': 'Esgauge', 'weight': 0.08141351}]",[],"[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Conference Board', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Esgauge', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Southwest Airlines', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Positive,,[],0
da099e4ef38445acbc68d851be2fe770,This is Morgan Stanley's favorite card issuer heading into second-quarter earnings,2023-07-18T10:54:09+00:00,MS,Financial Services,Capital Markets,"{'30_days_before': -0.01952540756531318, '5_days_before': -0.0014744970458455686, '3_days_before': 0.006878165383027657, '2_days_before': 0.006878165383027657, '1_days_before': 0.0030227828684781244, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.05737266710817268, '1_days_after': 0.013626745771483373, '2_days_after': 0.015559122415399806, '5_days_after': 0.01863538602998638, '30_days_after': -0.03741310197599068}",[],"[{'name': 'American Express earnings', 'weight': 0.099164866}, {'name': 'small businesses', 'weight': 0.089639165}, {'name': 'recent months', 'weight': 0.088314496}, {'name': 'higher revenue', 'weight': 0.087877184}, {'name': 'growing earnings', 'weight': 0.08702222}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.08476924}, {'name': 'robust revenue growth', 'weight': 0.07538231}, {'name': 'recent data', 'weight': 0.07331299}, {'name': 'American Express', 'weight': 0.072576314}, {'name': 'positive operating leverage', 'weight': 0.06802655}]","[{'name': 'Morgan Stanley'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': ""Morgan Stanley's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'AXP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Graseck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Betsy Graseck', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michael Bloom', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,Revenue Discussions,['revenue growth'],9
da099e4ef38445acbc68d851be2fe770,This is Morgan Stanley's favorite card issuer heading into second-quarter earnings,2023-07-18T10:54:09+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': 0.02195823675594033, '5_days_before': -0.0023898154294903495, '3_days_before': 0.011534673051668776, '2_days_before': 0.011534673051668776, '1_days_before': 0.007679290537119243, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.00799192260649817, '1_days_after': 0.0067004059743848154, '2_days_after': -0.032521624009465344, '5_days_after': -0.050249351497829164, '30_days_after': -0.0524281742652124}",[],"[{'name': 'American Express earnings', 'weight': 0.099164866}, {'name': 'small businesses', 'weight': 0.089639165}, {'name': 'recent months', 'weight': 0.088314496}, {'name': 'higher revenue', 'weight': 0.087877184}, {'name': 'growing earnings', 'weight': 0.08702222}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.08476924}, {'name': 'robust revenue growth', 'weight': 0.07538231}, {'name': 'recent data', 'weight': 0.07331299}, {'name': 'American Express', 'weight': 0.072576314}, {'name': 'positive operating leverage', 'weight': 0.06802655}]","[{'name': 'Morgan Stanley'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': ""Morgan Stanley's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'AXP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Graseck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Betsy Graseck', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michael Bloom', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,Revenue Discussions,['revenue growth'],9
da099e4ef38445acbc68d851be2fe770,This is Morgan Stanley's favorite card issuer heading into second-quarter earnings,2023-07-18T10:54:09+00:00,MS,Financial Services,Capital Markets,"{'30_days_before': -0.01952540756531318, '5_days_before': -0.0014744970458455686, '3_days_before': 0.006878165383027657, '2_days_before': 0.006878165383027657, '1_days_before': 0.0030227828684781244, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.05737266710817268, '1_days_after': 0.013626745771483373, '2_days_after': 0.015559122415399806, '5_days_after': 0.01863538602998638, '30_days_after': -0.03741310197599068}",[],"[{'name': 'American Express earnings', 'weight': 0.099164866}, {'name': 'small businesses', 'weight': 0.089639165}, {'name': 'recent months', 'weight': 0.088314496}, {'name': 'higher revenue', 'weight': 0.087877184}, {'name': 'growing earnings', 'weight': 0.08702222}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.08476924}, {'name': 'robust revenue growth', 'weight': 0.07538231}, {'name': 'recent data', 'weight': 0.07331299}, {'name': 'American Express', 'weight': 0.072576314}, {'name': 'positive operating leverage', 'weight': 0.06802655}]","[{'name': 'Morgan Stanley'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': ""Morgan Stanley's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'AXP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Graseck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Betsy Graseck', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michael Bloom', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
da099e4ef38445acbc68d851be2fe770,This is Morgan Stanley's favorite card issuer heading into second-quarter earnings,2023-07-18T10:54:09+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': 0.02195823675594033, '5_days_before': -0.0023898154294903495, '3_days_before': 0.011534673051668776, '2_days_before': 0.011534673051668776, '1_days_before': 0.007679290537119243, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.00799192260649817, '1_days_after': 0.0067004059743848154, '2_days_after': -0.032521624009465344, '5_days_after': -0.050249351497829164, '30_days_after': -0.0524281742652124}",[],"[{'name': 'American Express earnings', 'weight': 0.099164866}, {'name': 'small businesses', 'weight': 0.089639165}, {'name': 'recent months', 'weight': 0.088314496}, {'name': 'higher revenue', 'weight': 0.087877184}, {'name': 'growing earnings', 'weight': 0.08702222}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.08476924}, {'name': 'robust revenue growth', 'weight': 0.07538231}, {'name': 'recent data', 'weight': 0.07331299}, {'name': 'American Express', 'weight': 0.072576314}, {'name': 'positive operating leverage', 'weight': 0.06802655}]","[{'name': 'Morgan Stanley'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': ""Morgan Stanley's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'AXP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Graseck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Betsy Graseck', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michael Bloom', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Positive,,[],0
9660c99713614e139ff0594b7bbb64f7,Over 1.2million credit cards revealed on Dark Web in horrifying ‘BidenCash’ leak...,2022-10-11T13:28:10+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': -0.13210053678635192, '5_days_before': -0.03727187901727036, '3_days_before': -0.010719555858644592, '2_days_before': -0.010719555858644592, '1_days_before': -0.0032270922247427114, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.005355786498597137, '1_days_after': 0.013162362459837373, '2_days_after': 0.002642867050129505, '5_days_after': 0.010841132458482283, '30_days_after': 0.02078826037684922}","['https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/17105619/amazon-fire-stick-alexa-kindle-echo-ring-deals/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/20065013/woman-scammed-astronaut-marry-rocket-landing-fees/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/13721663/how-to-clear-cache-on-iphone/', 'https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/darkweb-market-bidencash-gives-away-12-million-credit-cards-for-free/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6237465/whatsapp-block-how-to-tell-profile/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/money/20057347/martin-lewis-calculate-running-cost-appliance/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/16484210/meta-meaning-facebook/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/13496857/how-to-change-your-facebook-password/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/topic/instagram/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/money/18135060/american-express-chaos-down-outage-payments/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/topic/facebook/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/money/14245702/nft-art-non-fungible-tokens-meaning/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/13470941/delete-instagram-account/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/topic/credit-cards/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/20057512/woman-allows-daughter-dye-hair-trolls-slammed/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/topic/whatsapp/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/phones-gadgets/11671735/onlyfans-app-banning-videos-content-october-shutting-down/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/14858659/what-does-pending-mean-on-snapchat/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/19794077/online-crooks-queens-death-scam/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/20067869/amazon-ring-doorbell-deal-cheap-2022-price/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/20008965/echo-dot-ring-doorbell-deal/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/15544736/how-to-drop-a-pin-on-google-maps/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/20062250/apple-iphone-5c-obsolete-warning/', 'https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/13950856/how-to-go-live-on-tiktok/']","[{'name': 'card numbers', 'weight': 0.1160757}, {'name': 'sensitive credit card information', 'weight': 0.107546695}, {'name': 'CREDIT card details', 'weight': 0.09629062}, {'name': 'compromised payment cards', 'weight': 0.09423158}, {'name': 'social security numbers', 'weight': 0.09411914}, {'name': 'card types', 'weight': 0.092423044}, {'name': 'CVV numbers', 'weight': 0.089880615}, {'name': 'Cards', 'weight': 0.08870726}, {'name': 'cardholder numbers', 'weight': 0.08870717}, {'name': 'bank names', 'weight': 0.067830645}]",[],"[{'data': 'BidenCash', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Bleeping Computer', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cyble', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Sun Online Tech & Science', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'India', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brazil', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mexico', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Turkey', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Spain', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Italy', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BidenCash', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Negative,,[],0
972c6fd2d28346b782cd266860dcffa2,‘Entertainment Tonight’s’ Kevin Frazier and Nischelle Turner to Host 2023 Palm Springs International Film Awards,2022-12-16T18:30:00+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': -0.040655775742143296, '5_days_before': -0.06517625996090315, '3_days_before': -0.014957181619055127, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.00018987850482221624, '1_days_after': -0.005259194860231409, '2_days_after': -0.002878206976404174, '5_days_after': 0.002988980033368893, '30_days_after': -0.00882214020277372}","['https://variety.com/t/palm-springs-international-film-festival/', 'https://variety.com/2022/film/news/baz-luhrmann-variety-10-directors-to-watch-palm-springs-film-festival-1235452656/', 'https://variety.com/2022/tv/news/daytime-emmys-hosts-kevin-frazier-nischelle-turner-1235285711/', 'https://variety.com/t/entertainment-tonight/', 'https://variety.com/2022/film/news/bill-nighy-palm-springs-international-film-awards-award-exclusive-1235455829/', 'https://variety.com/2022/film/festivals/rian-johnson-creative-impact-palm-springs-film-festival-1235458772/', 'https://variety.com/2022/film/news/angela-bassett-creative-impact-award-1235459936/']","[{'name': 'Palm Springs International Film Festival Film Awards', 'weight': 0.1101229}, {'name': 'Palm Springs International Film Awards', 'weight': 0.110074684}, {'name': 'Palm Springs', 'weight': 0.09880661}, {'name': 'the Palm Springs International Film Festival Film Awards gala', 'weight': 0.08291705}, {'name': 'Desert Palm Achievement', 'weight': 0.081255145}, {'name': 'top award season contenders', 'weight': 0.07668983}, {'name': 'filmmaker Rian Johnson', 'weight': 0.07524433}, {'name': '2023 Palm Springs International Film Awards', 'weight': 0.07442407}, {'name': 'The Palm Springs International Film Awards', 'weight': 0.07442407}, {'name': 'the Palm Spring International Film Festival', 'weight': 0.06625225}]",[{'name': 'Movies'}],"[{'data': 'Entertainment Tonight’s', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Emmy', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ET', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Elvis', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Till', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Breakthrough Performance', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tár', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Banshees of Inisherin', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Desert Palm Achievement', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Living', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Everything Everywhere All At Once', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the International Star awards', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'the Chairman’s Award', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Women Talking', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Black Panther: Wakanda Forever', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Glass Onion: A Knives Out Mystery', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kevin Frazier', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Nischelle Turner', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Mary Hart', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Harold Matzner', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Erin Johnson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Austin Butler', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Danielle Deadwyler', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cate Blanchett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Colin Farrell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bill Nighy', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michelle Yeoh', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Viola Davis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sarah Polley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steven Spielberg', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kristie Macosko Krieger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michelle Williams', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Paul Dano', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Seth Rogen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gabriel LaBelle', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Judd Hirsch', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Angela Bassett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Baz Luhrmann', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palm Springs International Film Awards', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Palm Spring International Film Festival', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palm Springs', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'PSIFF', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ET', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'IHG Hotels & Resorts', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'that night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Palm Springs Convention Center', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Parker', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
ccaaa03d3a15492e9d108cb75a280932,Taylor Swift set to bring The Eras Tour to Australia in 2024,2023-06-20T19:20:33+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': 0.10746197299812099, '5_days_before': -0.021643316166678472, '3_days_before': -0.01625915309492043, '2_days_before': -0.01625915309492043, '1_days_before': -0.011524045397297566, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.003550109295829218, '1_days_after': 0.006529805945837519, '2_days_after': 0.006529805945837519, '5_days_after': 0.000378336604279772, '30_days_after': -0.020129413578508837}","['https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/melbourne/index.html', 'https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/twitter/index.html', 'https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/taylor_swift/index.html', 'https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/sydney/index.html']","[{'name': 'Sydney shows', 'weight': 0.09608406}, {'name': 'Melbourne shows', 'weight': 0.09098055}, {'name': 'local time', 'weight': 0.08174421}, {'name': '-sale', 'weight': 0.07788098}, {'name': 'more Lana Del Rey vocals', 'weight': 0.07652004}, {'name': 'Shawn Mendes', 'weight': 0.07301683}, {'name': 'special guest Sabrina Carpenter', 'weight': 0.06773045}, {'name': 'sale', 'weight': 0.06488181}, {'name': 'Lana Del Rey', 'weight': 0.06442707}, {'name': 'VIP packages', 'weight': 0.06327343}]","[{'name': 'Taylor Swift'}, {'name': 'Australia'}]","[{'data': 'Taylor Swift', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Sabrina Carpenter', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Miles Teller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Aaron Rodgers', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Drew Barrymore', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jennifer Lawrence', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Camila Cabello', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shawn Mendes', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ice Spice', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Lana Del Rey', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Marcus Mumford', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jack Antonoff', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Eras Tour', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Frontier Touring', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Australia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Sydney', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Melbourne', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New Jersey', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shake It Off', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Midnights', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Til Dawn Edition', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Karma', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Snow On The Beach', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""You're Losing Me"", 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cruel Summer', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lover', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Melbourne Cricket Ground', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Accor Stadium', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '2am', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '2pm local time', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10am', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
f5ee57cc57fa4db4b54a2e493a5efd9d,Savers flock to credit card companies with their deposits,2023-05-13T18:24:47+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': -0.09367740701395244, '5_days_before': -0.04001683025739644, '3_days_before': 0.001177725881258973, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.011035125654538902, '1_days_after': 0.012905166425948078, '2_days_after': 0.012713655508776345, '5_days_after': 0.010619435888649997, '30_days_after': 0.09427445208879504}","['https://investors.synchrony.com/~/media/Files/S/Synchrony-Financial-IR-V3/press-release/q1-23-earnings-press-release.pdf', 'https://investor.capitalone.com/news-releases/news-release-details/capital-one-reports-first-quarter-2023-net-income-960-million-or', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdfhttps://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Supplement.pdf', 'https://s26.q4cdn.com/747928648/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Q1-2023-Earnings-Tables.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q1-2023-american-express-co-025933699.html', 'https://www.citigroup.com/global/news/press-release/2023/first-quarter-2023-results-key-metrics', 'https://twitter.com/__gabriellacruz', 'https://www08.wellsfargomedia.com/assets/pdf/about/investor-relations/earnings/first-quarter-2023-earnings.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/personal-finance', 'https://accountoffers.wellsfargo.com/savingsbonus/', 'https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_de702037a61396d96331e1b35d0fe508/bankofamerica/db/806/9848/earnings_release/The+Press+Release_1Q23_ADA.pdf', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/']","[{'name': 'deposits', 'weight': 0.0951644}, {'name': 'bank accounts', 'weight': 0.08309065}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08089244}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07539372}, {'name': 'higher returns', 'weight': 0.073745176}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.07023909}, {'name': 'credit card companies', 'weight': 0.06899785}, {'name': 'many store credit cards', 'weight': 0.06633033}, {'name': 'credit card offer', 'weight': 0.064627945}, {'name': 'Credit card issuers', 'weight': 0.06454045}]",[],"[{'data': 'Americans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Discover', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Synchrony Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capital One’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bank of America’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wells Fargo’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CitiGroup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LendingTree', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple Card’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Goldman Sachs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Way2Save', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matt Schulz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Gabriella', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
f5ee57cc57fa4db4b54a2e493a5efd9d,Savers flock to credit card companies with their deposits,2023-05-13T18:24:47+00:00,DFS,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': -0.0587129850011513, '5_days_before': -0.019583799410652802, '3_days_before': -0.004677776510385034, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.016048459636531343, '1_days_after': 0.011782792017537513, '2_days_after': 0.02319931792645824, '5_days_after': 0.0260260243171202, '30_days_after': 0.14907558777859942}","['https://investors.synchrony.com/~/media/Files/S/Synchrony-Financial-IR-V3/press-release/q1-23-earnings-press-release.pdf', 'https://investor.capitalone.com/news-releases/news-release-details/capital-one-reports-first-quarter-2023-net-income-960-million-or', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdfhttps://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Supplement.pdf', 'https://s26.q4cdn.com/747928648/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Q1-2023-Earnings-Tables.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q1-2023-american-express-co-025933699.html', 'https://www.citigroup.com/global/news/press-release/2023/first-quarter-2023-results-key-metrics', 'https://twitter.com/__gabriellacruz', 'https://www08.wellsfargomedia.com/assets/pdf/about/investor-relations/earnings/first-quarter-2023-earnings.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/personal-finance', 'https://accountoffers.wellsfargo.com/savingsbonus/', 'https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_de702037a61396d96331e1b35d0fe508/bankofamerica/db/806/9848/earnings_release/The+Press+Release_1Q23_ADA.pdf', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/']","[{'name': 'deposits', 'weight': 0.0951644}, {'name': 'bank accounts', 'weight': 0.08309065}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08089244}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07539372}, {'name': 'higher returns', 'weight': 0.073745176}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.07023909}, {'name': 'credit card companies', 'weight': 0.06899785}, {'name': 'many store credit cards', 'weight': 0.06633033}, {'name': 'credit card offer', 'weight': 0.064627945}, {'name': 'Credit card issuers', 'weight': 0.06454045}]",[],"[{'data': 'Americans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Discover', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Synchrony Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capital One’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bank of America’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wells Fargo’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CitiGroup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LendingTree', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple Card’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Goldman Sachs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Way2Save', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matt Schulz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Gabriella', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Positive,,[],0
f5ee57cc57fa4db4b54a2e493a5efd9d,Savers flock to credit card companies with their deposits,2023-05-13T18:24:47+00:00,AAPL,Technology,Consumer Electronics,"{'30_days_before': 0.04599414846628069, '5_days_before': 0.0015629751196186703, '3_days_before': -0.0038342129778750067, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.005855370985524688, '1_days_after': -0.008287704609560187, '2_days_after': -0.004129797182625516, '5_days_after': -0.0020135436059700584, '30_days_after': 0.004140563602808234}","['https://investors.synchrony.com/~/media/Files/S/Synchrony-Financial-IR-V3/press-release/q1-23-earnings-press-release.pdf', 'https://investor.capitalone.com/news-releases/news-release-details/capital-one-reports-first-quarter-2023-net-income-960-million-or', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdfhttps://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Supplement.pdf', 'https://s26.q4cdn.com/747928648/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Q1-2023-Earnings-Tables.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q1-2023-american-express-co-025933699.html', 'https://www.citigroup.com/global/news/press-release/2023/first-quarter-2023-results-key-metrics', 'https://twitter.com/__gabriellacruz', 'https://www08.wellsfargomedia.com/assets/pdf/about/investor-relations/earnings/first-quarter-2023-earnings.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/personal-finance', 'https://accountoffers.wellsfargo.com/savingsbonus/', 'https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_de702037a61396d96331e1b35d0fe508/bankofamerica/db/806/9848/earnings_release/The+Press+Release_1Q23_ADA.pdf', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/']","[{'name': 'deposits', 'weight': 0.0951644}, {'name': 'bank accounts', 'weight': 0.08309065}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08089244}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07539372}, {'name': 'higher returns', 'weight': 0.073745176}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.07023909}, {'name': 'credit card companies', 'weight': 0.06899785}, {'name': 'many store credit cards', 'weight': 0.06633033}, {'name': 'credit card offer', 'weight': 0.064627945}, {'name': 'Credit card issuers', 'weight': 0.06454045}]",[],"[{'data': 'Americans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Discover', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Synchrony Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capital One’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bank of America’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wells Fargo’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CitiGroup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LendingTree', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple Card’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Goldman Sachs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Way2Save', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matt Schulz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Gabriella', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
f5ee57cc57fa4db4b54a2e493a5efd9d,Savers flock to credit card companies with their deposits,2023-05-13T18:24:47+00:00,SYF,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': -0.08413692080976909, '5_days_before': -0.0183222555004392, '3_days_before': -0.010456032725190356, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.029907359334844674, '1_days_after': 0.01967292038902868, '2_days_after': 0.054591911404604954, '5_days_after': 0.056786223352821796, '30_days_after': 0.12255323376819005}","['https://investors.synchrony.com/~/media/Files/S/Synchrony-Financial-IR-V3/press-release/q1-23-earnings-press-release.pdf', 'https://investor.capitalone.com/news-releases/news-release-details/capital-one-reports-first-quarter-2023-net-income-960-million-or', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdfhttps://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Supplement.pdf', 'https://s26.q4cdn.com/747928648/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Q1-2023-Earnings-Tables.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q1-2023-american-express-co-025933699.html', 'https://www.citigroup.com/global/news/press-release/2023/first-quarter-2023-results-key-metrics', 'https://twitter.com/__gabriellacruz', 'https://www08.wellsfargomedia.com/assets/pdf/about/investor-relations/earnings/first-quarter-2023-earnings.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/personal-finance', 'https://accountoffers.wellsfargo.com/savingsbonus/', 'https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_de702037a61396d96331e1b35d0fe508/bankofamerica/db/806/9848/earnings_release/The+Press+Release_1Q23_ADA.pdf', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/']","[{'name': 'deposits', 'weight': 0.0951644}, {'name': 'bank accounts', 'weight': 0.08309065}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08089244}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07539372}, {'name': 'higher returns', 'weight': 0.073745176}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.07023909}, {'name': 'credit card companies', 'weight': 0.06899785}, {'name': 'many store credit cards', 'weight': 0.06633033}, {'name': 'credit card offer', 'weight': 0.064627945}, {'name': 'Credit card issuers', 'weight': 0.06454045}]",[],"[{'data': 'Americans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Discover', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Synchrony Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capital One’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bank of America’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wells Fargo’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CitiGroup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LendingTree', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple Card’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Goldman Sachs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Way2Save', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matt Schulz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Gabriella', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Positive,,[],0
f5ee57cc57fa4db4b54a2e493a5efd9d,Savers flock to credit card companies with their deposits,2023-05-13T18:24:47+00:00,WFC,Financial Services,Banks - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': -0.0468397658136559, '5_days_before': -0.0317283745567396, '3_days_before': -0.020331672613808416, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.03118432184357678, '1_days_after': 0.04202948600765377, '2_days_after': 0.02595995520790173, '5_days_after': 0.022748106553941216, '30_days_after': 0.02653943214386567}","['https://investors.synchrony.com/~/media/Files/S/Synchrony-Financial-IR-V3/press-release/q1-23-earnings-press-release.pdf', 'https://investor.capitalone.com/news-releases/news-release-details/capital-one-reports-first-quarter-2023-net-income-960-million-or', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdfhttps://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Supplement.pdf', 'https://s26.q4cdn.com/747928648/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Q1-2023-Earnings-Tables.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/q1-2023-american-express-co-025933699.html', 'https://www.citigroup.com/global/news/press-release/2023/first-quarter-2023-results-key-metrics', 'https://twitter.com/__gabriellacruz', 'https://www08.wellsfargomedia.com/assets/pdf/about/investor-relations/earnings/first-quarter-2023-earnings.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/personal-finance', 'https://accountoffers.wellsfargo.com/savingsbonus/', 'https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_de702037a61396d96331e1b35d0fe508/bankofamerica/db/806/9848/earnings_release/The+Press+Release_1Q23_ADA.pdf', 'https://s23.q4cdn.com/669804705/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/First-Quarter-2023-Earnings-Release.pdf', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/']","[{'name': 'deposits', 'weight': 0.0951644}, {'name': 'bank accounts', 'weight': 0.08309065}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08089244}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07539372}, {'name': 'higher returns', 'weight': 0.073745176}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.07023909}, {'name': 'credit card companies', 'weight': 0.06899785}, {'name': 'many store credit cards', 'weight': 0.06633033}, {'name': 'credit card offer', 'weight': 0.064627945}, {'name': 'Credit card issuers', 'weight': 0.06454045}]",[],"[{'data': 'Americans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Discover', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Synchrony Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capital One’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bank of America’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wells Fargo’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CitiGroup', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LendingTree', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple Card’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Goldman Sachs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Way2Save', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matt Schulz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Gabriella', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
4a457bd234f8421ca69ec48bf08d25d8,"Lisa Vanderpump, Karen Bronzo, Terry Crews, Dwight Caines and Marc Weinstock Join Variety’s Entertainment Marketing Summit 2023",2023-02-15T20:44:50+00:00,CMG,Consumer Cyclical,Restaurants,"{'30_days_before': 0.08859255771169416, '5_days_before': 0.04586805745805256, '3_days_before': 0.03441944811528641, '2_days_before': 0.02644009960343552, '1_days_before': 0.004535899525163867, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.007520659503841176, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': -0.018777305665073074, '30_days_after': 0.034366594621555446}",['http://VARIETY.COM/ENTMAR'],"[{'name': 'chief marketing officer', 'weight': 0.09956605}, {'name': 'marketing', 'weight': 0.08063985}, {'name': 'digital marketing', 'weight': 0.0805191}, {'name': 'intersectional marketing', 'weight': 0.08050387}, {'name': 'multicultural marketing', 'weight': 0.08048679}, {'name': 'experiential marketing', 'weight': 0.08013602}, {'name': 'worldwide marketing', 'weight': 0.079272166}, {'name': 'domestic marketing', 'weight': 0.07924754}, {'name': 'chief business officer', 'weight': 0.07802131}, {'name': 'chief franchise officer', 'weight': 0.07465932}]",[{'name': 'Lisa Vanderpump'}],"[{'data': 'Lisa Vanderpump', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Karen Bronzo', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Terry Crews', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Dwight Caines', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Marc Weinstock', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Claudia Eller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kate Aurthur', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jana Arbanas', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dea Lawrence', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Paige', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zach Enterlin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Margaret Walker', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ellene V. Miles', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Christine Benetiz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Claudia Chagui', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tressie Lieberman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'A.J. Feliciano', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Wilson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steve Raizes', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jill Wilfert', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Josh Silverman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shiz Suzuki', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dave Tinson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zach Greenberger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Variety', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Deloitte', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Warner Bros. Discovery', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Universal Pictures', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Paramount Pictures', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'BET', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'HBO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NBCUniversal Television and Streaming', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NBCUniversal Telemundo Enterprises', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chipotle Mexican Grill', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rooster Teeth Network', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SiriusXM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LEGO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mattel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lyft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Entertainment Marketing Summit 2023', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'a Keynote Entertainment Marketing Roundtable', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Los Angeles', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vanderpump Rules', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America’s Got Talent', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Breakthrough TV Branding', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Multicultural Marketing Unlocking Younger Generations', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Winning in the Coming Peak Creator Economy', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brandmaker Visionaries – Building Storytelling Universes', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Industry Competitiveness,Causal,Positive,,[],0
4a457bd234f8421ca69ec48bf08d25d8,"Lisa Vanderpump, Karen Bronzo, Terry Crews, Dwight Caines and Marc Weinstock Join Variety’s Entertainment Marketing Summit 2023",2023-02-15T20:44:50+00:00,PARA,Communication Services,Entertainment,"{'30_days_before': 0.22536052081835445, '5_days_before': 0.13663752157261366, '3_days_before': 0.12518891222984752, '2_days_before': 0.10023560534151654, '1_days_before': 0.09032259080948779, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.028591108373116403, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': 0.005120597762478085, '30_days_after': -0.11848490918685295}",['http://VARIETY.COM/ENTMAR'],"[{'name': 'chief marketing officer', 'weight': 0.09956605}, {'name': 'marketing', 'weight': 0.08063985}, {'name': 'digital marketing', 'weight': 0.0805191}, {'name': 'intersectional marketing', 'weight': 0.08050387}, {'name': 'multicultural marketing', 'weight': 0.08048679}, {'name': 'experiential marketing', 'weight': 0.08013602}, {'name': 'worldwide marketing', 'weight': 0.079272166}, {'name': 'domestic marketing', 'weight': 0.07924754}, {'name': 'chief business officer', 'weight': 0.07802131}, {'name': 'chief franchise officer', 'weight': 0.07465932}]",[{'name': 'Lisa Vanderpump'}],"[{'data': 'Lisa Vanderpump', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Karen Bronzo', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Terry Crews', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Dwight Caines', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Marc Weinstock', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Claudia Eller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kate Aurthur', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jana Arbanas', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dea Lawrence', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Paige', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zach Enterlin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Margaret Walker', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ellene V. Miles', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Christine Benetiz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Claudia Chagui', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tressie Lieberman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'A.J. Feliciano', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Wilson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steve Raizes', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jill Wilfert', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Josh Silverman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shiz Suzuki', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dave Tinson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zach Greenberger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Variety', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Deloitte', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Warner Bros. Discovery', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Universal Pictures', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Paramount Pictures', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'BET', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'HBO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NBCUniversal Television and Streaming', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NBCUniversal Telemundo Enterprises', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chipotle Mexican Grill', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rooster Teeth Network', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SiriusXM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LEGO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mattel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lyft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Entertainment Marketing Summit 2023', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'a Keynote Entertainment Marketing Roundtable', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Los Angeles', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vanderpump Rules', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America’s Got Talent', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Breakthrough TV Branding', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Multicultural Marketing Unlocking Younger Generations', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Winning in the Coming Peak Creator Economy', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brandmaker Visionaries – Building Storytelling Universes', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Industry Competitiveness,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
4a457bd234f8421ca69ec48bf08d25d8,"Lisa Vanderpump, Karen Bronzo, Terry Crews, Dwight Caines and Marc Weinstock Join Variety’s Entertainment Marketing Summit 2023",2023-02-15T20:44:50+00:00,AXP,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': 0.1619560357307881, '5_days_before': 0.00792185661188416, '3_days_before': -0.003526752730881988, '2_days_before': -0.0033594894735646808, '1_days_before': -0.004706763451271856, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0013215653282272477, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': 0.006918815846226889, '30_days_after': -0.07737743273283071}",['http://VARIETY.COM/ENTMAR'],"[{'name': 'chief marketing officer', 'weight': 0.09956605}, {'name': 'marketing', 'weight': 0.08063985}, {'name': 'digital marketing', 'weight': 0.0805191}, {'name': 'intersectional marketing', 'weight': 0.08050387}, {'name': 'multicultural marketing', 'weight': 0.08048679}, {'name': 'experiential marketing', 'weight': 0.08013602}, {'name': 'worldwide marketing', 'weight': 0.079272166}, {'name': 'domestic marketing', 'weight': 0.07924754}, {'name': 'chief business officer', 'weight': 0.07802131}, {'name': 'chief franchise officer', 'weight': 0.07465932}]",[{'name': 'Lisa Vanderpump'}],"[{'data': 'Lisa Vanderpump', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Karen Bronzo', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Terry Crews', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Dwight Caines', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Marc Weinstock', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Claudia Eller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kate Aurthur', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jana Arbanas', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dea Lawrence', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Paige', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zach Enterlin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Margaret Walker', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ellene V. Miles', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Christine Benetiz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Claudia Chagui', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tressie Lieberman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'A.J. Feliciano', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Wilson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steve Raizes', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jill Wilfert', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Josh Silverman', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shiz Suzuki', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dave Tinson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zach Greenberger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Variety', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Deloitte', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Warner Bros. Discovery', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Universal Pictures', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Paramount Pictures', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'BET', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'HBO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NBCUniversal Television and Streaming', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NBCUniversal Telemundo Enterprises', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chipotle Mexican Grill', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rooster Teeth Network', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SiriusXM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LEGO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mattel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lyft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Entertainment Marketing Summit 2023', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'a Keynote Entertainment Marketing Roundtable', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Los Angeles', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vanderpump Rules', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America’s Got Talent', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Breakthrough TV Branding', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Multicultural Marketing Unlocking Younger Generations', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Winning in the Coming Peak Creator Economy', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brandmaker Visionaries – Building Storytelling Universes', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Industry Competitiveness,Causal,Positive,,[],0
bd480300e53547669531d86772c5a6fa,AIG's Zaffino gets 5-year extension as CEO,2022-11-10T22:42:00+00:00,AIG,Financial Services,Insurance - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': 0.2642689344579927, '5_days_before': 0.046097988704839166, '3_days_before': 0.018400615281988886, '2_days_before': 0.04546914553071668, '1_days_before': -0.018999389217613016, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.012541487396120932, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.006451875479685842, '5_days_after': -0.0041181192672372635, '30_days_after': 0.05225776291413997}","['https://www.reuters.com/companies/AIG.N', 'https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/about-us/trust-principles.html']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.13770053}, {'name': 'Peter Zaffino', 'weight': 0.13080741}, {'name': 'Shailesh Kuber', 'weight': 0.12627226}, {'name': 'CEO', 'weight': 0.106933534}, {'name': 'Zaffino', 'weight': 0.100639515}, {'name': 'Nov.', 'weight': 0.096972756}, {'name': 'Insurer American International Group Incs (AIG.N) Chief Executive Officer Peter Zaffino', 'weight': 0.089615025}, {'name': 'AIG.N', 'weight': 0.084612675}, {'name': 'Insurer American International Group Incs', 'weight': 0.08089098}, {'name': 'Mehnaz Yasmin', 'weight': 0.07474951}]","[{'name': 'Business Leaders'}, {'name': 'AIG'}]","[{'data': 'AIG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Reuters', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Insurer American International Group Inc's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zaffino', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mehnaz Yasmin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shailesh Kuber', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bengaluru', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
f9c5c361946148d0acaa3bcc99ff7a07,Insurer AIG profit beats estimates on gains in life and retirement unit,2023-08-01T20:19:41+00:00,TRV,Financial Services,Insurance - Property & Casualty,"{'30_days_before': -0.008944481884901156, '5_days_before': -0.024517232915679643, '3_days_before': -0.005483110691314685, '2_days_before': -0.006951823631833998, '1_days_before': 0.000926996933075408, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006817365047829593, '1_days_after': 0.000872646349743933, '2_days_after': 0.000872646349743933, '5_days_after': -0.008415207498763011, '30_days_after': -0.04499578766620482}","['https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/AIG.N', 'https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/TRV.N', 'https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/about-us/trust-principles.html']","[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.08956689}, {'name': 'catastrophe losses', 'weight': 0.08690921}, {'name': 'Insurer AIG profit', 'weight': 0.07958052}, {'name': 'higher income', 'weight': 0.07912105}, {'name': 'fixed index annuities', 'weight': 0.07815074}, {'name': 'net premiums', 'weight': 0.07392374}, {'name': 'AIGs general insurance accident year combined ratio', 'weight': 0.07325488}, {'name': 'Total consolidated net investment income', 'weight': 0.07323997}, {'name': 'global insured losses', 'weight': 0.07182548}, {'name': 'peer insurer Travelers Companies', 'weight': 0.07019818}]",[{'name': 'AIG'}],"[{'data': 'AIG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Reuters', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American International Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gallagher Re', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Travelers Companies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TRV.N', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Guam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the United States', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Typhoon Mawar', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Western Pacific Island', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
f9c5c361946148d0acaa3bcc99ff7a07,Insurer AIG profit beats estimates on gains in life and retirement unit,2023-08-01T20:19:41+00:00,AIG,Financial Services,Insurance - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': 0.048186393117715776, '5_days_before': -0.014165384332600839, '3_days_before': 0.0036569605769347646, '2_days_before': 0.0021882476364154524, '1_days_before': 0.004324109880381566, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.02857946725908933, '1_days_after': -0.002060067440370017, '2_days_after': -0.002060067440370017, '5_days_after': 0.006445700518875941, '30_days_after': -0.03415937596614771}","['https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/AIG.N', 'https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/TRV.N', 'https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/about-us/trust-principles.html']","[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.08956689}, {'name': 'catastrophe losses', 'weight': 0.08690921}, {'name': 'Insurer AIG profit', 'weight': 0.07958052}, {'name': 'higher income', 'weight': 0.07912105}, {'name': 'fixed index annuities', 'weight': 0.07815074}, {'name': 'net premiums', 'weight': 0.07392374}, {'name': 'AIGs general insurance accident year combined ratio', 'weight': 0.07325488}, {'name': 'Total consolidated net investment income', 'weight': 0.07323997}, {'name': 'global insured losses', 'weight': 0.07182548}, {'name': 'peer insurer Travelers Companies', 'weight': 0.07019818}]",[{'name': 'AIG'}],"[{'data': 'AIG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Reuters', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American International Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gallagher Re', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Travelers Companies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TRV.N', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Guam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the United States', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Typhoon Mawar', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Western Pacific Island', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,,[],0
f9c5c361946148d0acaa3bcc99ff7a07,Insurer AIG profit beats estimates on gains in life and retirement unit,2023-08-01T20:19:41+00:00,TRV,Financial Services,Insurance - Property & Casualty,"{'30_days_before': -0.008944481884901156, '5_days_before': -0.024517232915679643, '3_days_before': -0.005483110691314685, '2_days_before': -0.006951823631833998, '1_days_before': 0.000926996933075408, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006817365047829593, '1_days_after': 0.000872646349743933, '2_days_after': 0.000872646349743933, '5_days_after': -0.008415207498763011, '30_days_after': -0.04499578766620482}","['https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/AIG.N', 'https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/TRV.N', 'https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/about-us/trust-principles.html']","[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.08956689}, {'name': 'catastrophe losses', 'weight': 0.08690921}, {'name': 'Insurer AIG profit', 'weight': 0.07958052}, {'name': 'higher income', 'weight': 0.07912105}, {'name': 'fixed index annuities', 'weight': 0.07815074}, {'name': 'net premiums', 'weight': 0.07392374}, {'name': 'AIGs general insurance accident year combined ratio', 'weight': 0.07325488}, {'name': 'Total consolidated net investment income', 'weight': 0.07323997}, {'name': 'global insured losses', 'weight': 0.07182548}, {'name': 'peer insurer Travelers Companies', 'weight': 0.07019818}]",[{'name': 'AIG'}],"[{'data': 'AIG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Reuters', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American International Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gallagher Re', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Travelers Companies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TRV.N', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Guam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the United States', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Typhoon Mawar', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Western Pacific Island', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
f9c5c361946148d0acaa3bcc99ff7a07,Insurer AIG profit beats estimates on gains in life and retirement unit,2023-08-01T20:19:41+00:00,AIG,Financial Services,Insurance - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': 0.048186393117715776, '5_days_before': -0.014165384332600839, '3_days_before': 0.0036569605769347646, '2_days_before': 0.0021882476364154524, '1_days_before': 0.004324109880381566, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.02857946725908933, '1_days_after': -0.002060067440370017, '2_days_after': -0.002060067440370017, '5_days_after': 0.006445700518875941, '30_days_after': -0.03415937596614771}","['https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/AIG.N', 'https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies/TRV.N', 'https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/about-us/trust-principles.html']","[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.08956689}, {'name': 'catastrophe losses', 'weight': 0.08690921}, {'name': 'Insurer AIG profit', 'weight': 0.07958052}, {'name': 'higher income', 'weight': 0.07912105}, {'name': 'fixed index annuities', 'weight': 0.07815074}, {'name': 'net premiums', 'weight': 0.07392374}, {'name': 'AIGs general insurance accident year combined ratio', 'weight': 0.07325488}, {'name': 'Total consolidated net investment income', 'weight': 0.07323997}, {'name': 'global insured losses', 'weight': 0.07182548}, {'name': 'peer insurer Travelers Companies', 'weight': 0.07019818}]",[{'name': 'AIG'}],"[{'data': 'AIG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Reuters', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American International Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gallagher Re', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Travelers Companies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TRV.N', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Guam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the United States', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Typhoon Mawar', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Western Pacific Island', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Positive,,[],0
07e800c55ae04b7dabb7c752970a9050,AIG Finance Chief Takes Temporary Medical Leave,2023-01-10T22:23:00+00:00,AIG,Financial Services,Insurance - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': 0.0058945326985100355, '5_days_before': -0.023785414419216222, '3_days_before': -0.017041047712620938, '2_days_before': -0.016273415167357808, '1_days_before': -0.01355413727399668, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.012691826480166313, '1_days_after': 0.007466749191169297, '2_days_after': 0.007466749191169297, '5_days_after': -0.0003879003364706257, '30_days_after': -0.06399615721348328}",['https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/AIG'],"[{'name': 'Temporary Medical Leave', 'weight': 0.15668964}, {'name': 'Chief Financial Officer Shane Fitzsimons', 'weight': 0.14131479}, {'name': 'absence', 'weight': 0.1305474}, {'name': 'the interim CFO', 'weight': 0.11995967}, {'name': 'Shane Fitzsimons', 'weight': 0.11549102}, {'name': 'portfolio management', 'weight': 0.09626599}, {'name': 'a temporary medical leave', 'weight': 0.09247335}, {'name': 'the company’s CFO', 'weight': 0.07758349}, {'name': 'American International Group Inc.', 'weight': 0.07473835}, {'name': 'Tuesday', 'weight': 0.07472537}]",[{'name': 'AIG'}],"[{'data': 'AIG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American International Group Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shane Fitzsimons', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mark Lyons', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
a67ce91dbd934176b7a63836f7b3b7da,"Dow futures steady after snapping rally, Intel lifts 8.4% after earnings",2023-07-27T19:32:02+00:00,PG,Consumer Defensive,Household & Personal Products,"{'30_days_before': 0.0206739827410255, '5_days_before': -0.005361865840512459, '3_days_before': -0.011353246531809136, '2_days_before': -0.010704254346702191, '1_days_before': -0.005463039647031986, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.018391122408956573, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.0021719099059893665, '5_days_after': 0.021305170516156213, '30_days_after': 0.015684733158727426}","['https://www.investing.com/equities/enphase-energy-inc-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/pce-price-index-906?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/roku-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/subway-tuna-lawsuit-is-being-dismissed-3136787?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/earnings-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-sentiment-320?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/sweetgreen-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/walmart-in-mexico-posts-5-rise-in-q2-net-profit-3136749?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/dow-futures-steady-after-snapping-rally-intel-lifts-84-after-earnings-3136783?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-expectations-900?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/economic-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/intel-corp-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance']","[{'name': 'expected losses', 'weight': 0.17275992}, {'name': 'Q2 losses', 'weight': 0.1266261}, {'name': 'share', 'weight': 0.12037803}, {'name': 'corporate earnings results', 'weight': 0.10334253}, {'name': 'better than expected macroeconomic releases', 'weight': 0.08723783}, {'name': 'quarterly results', 'weight': 0.08441497}, {'name': 'Revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenues', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'Q2 EPS', 'weight': 0.07801429}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}]","[{'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NASDAQ', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'INTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ROKU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'SG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Enphase Energy Inc', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Exxon Mobil Corp', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'XOM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Procter & Gamble Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AstraZeneca PLC ADR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '6:50pm ET', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10:50pm GMT', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
a67ce91dbd934176b7a63836f7b3b7da,"Dow futures steady after snapping rally, Intel lifts 8.4% after earnings",2023-07-27T19:32:02+00:00,ENPH,Technology,Solar,"{'30_days_before': 0.03618593606992626, '5_days_before': -0.06017575463646496, '3_days_before': -0.06473467030340252, '2_days_before': -0.07044130753863709, '1_days_before': -0.0314156519759935, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.08463804059183333, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.017667766723572842, '5_days_after': -0.07298740654231706, '30_days_after': -0.15560396166018065}","['https://www.investing.com/equities/enphase-energy-inc-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/pce-price-index-906?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/roku-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/subway-tuna-lawsuit-is-being-dismissed-3136787?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/earnings-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-sentiment-320?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/sweetgreen-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/walmart-in-mexico-posts-5-rise-in-q2-net-profit-3136749?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/dow-futures-steady-after-snapping-rally-intel-lifts-84-after-earnings-3136783?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-expectations-900?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/economic-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/intel-corp-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance']","[{'name': 'expected losses', 'weight': 0.17275992}, {'name': 'Q2 losses', 'weight': 0.1266261}, {'name': 'share', 'weight': 0.12037803}, {'name': 'corporate earnings results', 'weight': 0.10334253}, {'name': 'better than expected macroeconomic releases', 'weight': 0.08723783}, {'name': 'quarterly results', 'weight': 0.08441497}, {'name': 'Revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenues', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'Q2 EPS', 'weight': 0.07801429}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}]","[{'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NASDAQ', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'INTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ROKU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'SG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Enphase Energy Inc', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Exxon Mobil Corp', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'XOM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Procter & Gamble Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AstraZeneca PLC ADR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '6:50pm ET', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10:50pm GMT', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
a67ce91dbd934176b7a63836f7b3b7da,"Dow futures steady after snapping rally, Intel lifts 8.4% after earnings",2023-07-27T19:32:02+00:00,INTC,Technology,Semiconductors,"{'30_days_before': 0.013550472971201821, '5_days_before': 0.015578988921072234, '3_days_before': 0.02454170974891068, '2_days_before': 0.013351835179562066, '1_days_before': 0.011954344210247991, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.0561136086083327, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.030249759968190126, '5_days_after': -0.035684575915882366, '30_days_after': -0.05137381965620513}","['https://www.investing.com/equities/enphase-energy-inc-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/pce-price-index-906?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/roku-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/subway-tuna-lawsuit-is-being-dismissed-3136787?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/earnings-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-sentiment-320?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/sweetgreen-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/walmart-in-mexico-posts-5-rise-in-q2-net-profit-3136749?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/dow-futures-steady-after-snapping-rally-intel-lifts-84-after-earnings-3136783?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-expectations-900?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/economic-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/intel-corp-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance']","[{'name': 'expected losses', 'weight': 0.17275992}, {'name': 'Q2 losses', 'weight': 0.1266261}, {'name': 'share', 'weight': 0.12037803}, {'name': 'corporate earnings results', 'weight': 0.10334253}, {'name': 'better than expected macroeconomic releases', 'weight': 0.08723783}, {'name': 'quarterly results', 'weight': 0.08441497}, {'name': 'Revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenues', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'Q2 EPS', 'weight': 0.07801429}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}]","[{'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NASDAQ', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'INTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ROKU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'SG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Enphase Energy Inc', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Exxon Mobil Corp', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'XOM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Procter & Gamble Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AstraZeneca PLC ADR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '6:50pm ET', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10:50pm GMT', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,,[],0
a67ce91dbd934176b7a63836f7b3b7da,"Dow futures steady after snapping rally, Intel lifts 8.4% after earnings",2023-07-27T19:32:02+00:00,AON,Financial Services,Insurance Brokers,"{'30_days_before': 0.010604462107505097, '5_days_before': -0.011264421876883035, '3_days_before': -0.018899034837126072, '2_days_before': -0.017763726069862873, '1_days_before': -0.005853749663485175, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.06102581484698666, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.003677448135070205, '5_days_after': 0.011627621631677743, '30_days_after': 0.07104829027225579}","['https://www.investing.com/equities/enphase-energy-inc-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/pce-price-index-906?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/roku-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/subway-tuna-lawsuit-is-being-dismissed-3136787?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/earnings-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-sentiment-320?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/sweetgreen-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/walmart-in-mexico-posts-5-rise-in-q2-net-profit-3136749?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/dow-futures-steady-after-snapping-rally-intel-lifts-84-after-earnings-3136783?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-expectations-900?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/economic-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/intel-corp-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance']","[{'name': 'expected losses', 'weight': 0.17275992}, {'name': 'Q2 losses', 'weight': 0.1266261}, {'name': 'share', 'weight': 0.12037803}, {'name': 'corporate earnings results', 'weight': 0.10334253}, {'name': 'better than expected macroeconomic releases', 'weight': 0.08723783}, {'name': 'quarterly results', 'weight': 0.08441497}, {'name': 'Revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenues', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'Q2 EPS', 'weight': 0.07801429}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}]","[{'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NASDAQ', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'INTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ROKU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'SG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Enphase Energy Inc', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Exxon Mobil Corp', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'XOM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Procter & Gamble Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AstraZeneca PLC ADR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '6:50pm ET', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10:50pm GMT', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
a67ce91dbd934176b7a63836f7b3b7da,"Dow futures steady after snapping rally, Intel lifts 8.4% after earnings",2023-07-27T19:32:02+00:00,XOM,Energy,Oil & Gas Integrated,"{'30_days_before': 0.008675317435050567, '5_days_before': 0.014727058162217421, '3_days_before': -0.0037624839636815066, '2_days_before': -0.0023048539423217163, '1_days_before': 0.00956487134912376, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.021829953140274472, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.028101196043123444, '5_days_after': 0.04595072094160502, '30_days_after': 0.08909347503444942}","['https://www.investing.com/equities/enphase-energy-inc-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/pce-price-index-906?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/roku-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/subway-tuna-lawsuit-is-being-dismissed-3136787?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/earnings-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-sentiment-320?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/sweetgreen-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/walmart-in-mexico-posts-5-rise-in-q2-net-profit-3136749?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/dow-futures-steady-after-snapping-rally-intel-lifts-84-after-earnings-3136783?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://www.investing.com/economic-calendar/michigan-consumer-expectations-900?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance', 'https://au.investing.com/economic-calendar/', 'https://www.investing.com/equities/intel-corp-earnings?utm_source=yahoo&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=yahoo_finance']","[{'name': 'expected losses', 'weight': 0.17275992}, {'name': 'Q2 losses', 'weight': 0.1266261}, {'name': 'share', 'weight': 0.12037803}, {'name': 'corporate earnings results', 'weight': 0.10334253}, {'name': 'better than expected macroeconomic releases', 'weight': 0.08723783}, {'name': 'quarterly results', 'weight': 0.08441497}, {'name': 'Revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenue', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'revenues', 'weight': 0.08083953}, {'name': 'Q2 EPS', 'weight': 0.07801429}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}]","[{'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NASDAQ', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'INTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ROKU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'SG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Enphase Energy Inc', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Exxon Mobil Corp', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'XOM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Procter & Gamble Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AstraZeneca PLC ADR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '6:50pm ET', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '10:50pm GMT', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
0de52dcf76d04aac8402f9f51728b120,Arthur J. Gallagher (AJG) Expands in Ireland With Buyout,2022-11-07T15:25:03+00:00,AJG,Financial Services,Insurance Brokers,"{'30_days_before': 0.08077555020939142, '5_days_before': 0.030177465841119355, '3_days_before': -0.00806775860433917, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.009495475120859131, '1_days_after': 0.0009743593131797956, '2_days_after': -0.03033414517748856, '5_days_after': -0.07626900681412085, '30_days_after': -0.019044438079008907}","['https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=AJG&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_255&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|company_news_-_finance_sector-2014842', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZR&d_alert=rd_final_rank&t=ERIE&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_255&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|company_news_-_finance_sector-2014842', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp/?ALERT=RPT_7BEST_YHOSYND&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_7BEST_ANALYSTBLOG_255&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|company_news_-_finance_sector-2014842', 'https://www.zacks.com/', 'https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2014842/arthur-j-gallagher-ajg-expands-in-ireland-with-buyout?cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|company_news_-_finance_sector-2014842', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=AXS&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_255&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|company_news_-_finance_sector-2014842', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZR&d_alert=rd_final_rank&t=RYAN&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_255&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|company_news_-_finance_sector-2014842']","[{'name': 'estimated annualized revenues', 'weight': 0.09091205}, {'name': 'annualized revenues', 'weight': 0.08788517}, {'name': 'Free Stock Analysis Report', 'weight': 0.08066136}, {'name': 'organic revenue improvement', 'weight': 0.07740161}, {'name': 'Axis Capital Holdings Limited AXS', 'weight': 0.075029746}, {'name': 'Axis Capital Holdings Limited', 'weight': 0.07167052}, {'name': 'Erie Indemnity Company ERIE', 'weight': 0.07097968}, {'name': 'Ryan Specialty Holdings Inc. RYAN', 'weight': 0.06806832}, {'name': 'better growth opportunities', 'weight': 0.06658257}, {'name': 'Erie Indemnity Company', 'weight': 0.06656712}]",[],"[{'data': 'Arthur J. Gallagher', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'AJG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Doyle Insurance Brokers (Wexford) Limited', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Commercial & Agricultural Insurance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Erie Indemnity Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Ryan Specialty Holdings Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Axis Capital Holdings Limited AXS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Zacks', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'AXS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ireland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Causal,Positive,Mergers and Acquisitions,"['acquisition', 'merger', 'strategic merger']",23
4d06b11acfa348858d7a265dfc4f674e,Bank of America Sweetens Yield on Gabon Blue Bond Sale to Lure Investors,2023-08-07T19:28:38.169000+00:00,BAC,Financial Services,Banks - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': 0.11742014046130822, '5_days_before': 0.024670335120690057, '3_days_before': 0.01853034253620267, '2_days_before': 0.01853034253620267, '1_days_before': 0.00950624975683989, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.014915900833623486, '1_days_after': 0.0023415976144920414, '2_days_after': 0.014753128092500845, '5_days_after': -0.002658229555937419, '30_days_after': -0.0710652786987298}","['https://www.bloomberg.com/news/terminal/RZ1798DWLU68', 'https://www.dfc.gov/what-we-offer/our-products/political-risk-insurance', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/quote/1779161D:US', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-21/gabon-is-in-talks-to-fund-marine-conservation-through-debt-swap', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-03/bofa-led-gabon-blue-bond-sale-faces-delays-on-market-volatility', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/terminal/RYCY5FMRXLVR', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/quote/BAC:US', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/terminal/RYRK4TDWLU68', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-09/ecuador-to-reap-1-billion-savings-from-record-debt-nature-swap', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/quote/ZI029048:Corp', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/terminal/RYCU79T0AFB4', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-11-07/debt-for-nature-swaps-offer-option-for-developing-countries', 'https://www.nature.org/en-us/', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/quote/1506186Z:US', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-11/bank-of-america-to-lead-500-million-debt-nature-swap-for-gabon']","[{'name': 'Gabon Blue Bond Sale', 'weight': 0.08420382}, {'name': 'financial markets', 'weight': 0.08400036}, {'name': 'market volatility', 'weight': 0.08375691}, {'name': 'investor interest', 'weight': 0.07966344}, {'name': 'Bloomberg', 'weight': 0.07855654}, {'name': 'initial price talk', 'weight': 0.06939485}, {'name': 'marine conservation', 'weight': 0.064686365}, {'name': 'political risk insurance', 'weight': 0.06393895}, {'name': 'adviser', 'weight': 0.06336767}, {'name': 'limited access', 'weight': 0.06253664}]",[{'name': 'Bank of America'}],"[{'data': 'Bank of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Bloomberg', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Nature Conservancy', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Moody’s Investors Service', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Gabon', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ecuador', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'African', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Galapagos Islands', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
d296cda8e54e47b9ac9a79b5b963adf9,"Bank of America raked in at least $80 million by repeatedly charging some customers a $35 fee, regulators say",2023-07-12T05:09:21+00:00,BAC,Financial Services,Banks - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': -0.01786223273781773, '5_days_before': 0.02903204002716897, '3_days_before': 0.017174958965454623, '2_days_before': 0.014769932908323291, '1_days_before': 0.005818994754078544, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.004304807660289844, '1_days_after': -0.017849777568553216, '2_days_after': -0.017849777568553216, '5_days_after': 0.024750777328854223, '30_days_after': 0.06479793988789462}","['https://www.businessinsider.com/terms', 'https://www.consumerfinance.gov/enforcement/actions/bank-of-america-n-a-fees/', 'https://www.consumerfinance.gov/about-us/newsroom/cfpb-orders-bank-of-america-to-pay-727-million-in-consumer-relief-for-illegal-credit-card-practices/', 'https://www.businessinsider.com/bank-of-america-secretly-issued-credit-cards-without-consent-cfpb-2023-7', 'https://www.consumerfinance.gov/about-us/newsroom/bank-of-america-for-illegally-charging-junk-fees-withholding-credit-card-rewards-opening-fake-accounts/', 'https://newsroom.bankofamerica.com/content/newsroom/press-releases/2022/01/bank-of-america-announces-sweeping-changes-to-overdraft-services.html', 'https://www.businessinsider.com/privacy-policy', 'https://www.businessinsider.com/bank-of-america-fined-botching-unemployment-benefits-aid-pandemic-money-2022-7']","[{'name': 'CFPB Director Rohit Chopra', 'weight': 0.10867079}, {'name': 'fees', 'weight': 0.0976491}, {'name': 'overdraft fees', 'weight': 0.09534195}, {'name': 'customer trust', 'weight': 0.0952804}, {'name': 'customers', 'weight': 0.09340925}, {'name': 'Rohit Chopra', 'weight': 0.08800242}, {'name': 'credit card accounts', 'weight': 0.08302963}, {'name': 'CFPB', 'weight': 0.08127823}, {'name': 'credit card rewards', 'weight': 0.07716176}, {'name': 'declined transactions', 'weight': 0.07319155}]",[{'name': 'Bank of America'}],"[{'data': 'Bank of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'CFPB', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'the Consumer Finance Protection Bureau', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Insider', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Haldin', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rohit Chopra', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'William Haldin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the COVID-19 pandemic', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Negative,,[],0
572354b1a9da46acb924b8e6e79bd272,Bank of America Says Millions Will Pay For This Service Within a Year,2023-03-10T18:07:00+00:00,BAC,Financial Services,Banks - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': -0.1437233230012671, '5_days_before': -0.08414207972143894, '3_days_before': 0.005637317001037645, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0566335916820474, '1_days_after': -0.002407246523967066, '2_days_after': -0.0031567524548856696, '5_days_after': -0.03200814800614149, '30_days_after': -0.06485504365976791}",['https://www.thestreet.com/investing/bank-of-america-says-millions-will-pay-for-social-media-by-2024?puc=yahoo&cm_ven=YAHOO'],"[{'name': 'new revenue', 'weight': 0.12532733}, {'name': 'America analysts', 'weight': 0.121944}, {'name': 'CNBC', 'weight': 0.105763935}, {'name': 'researchers', 'weight': 0.088959344}, {'name': 'its paid subscription service', 'weight': 0.086613245}, {'name': 'businesses', 'weight': 0.08361979}, {'name': 'consumers', 'weight': 0.07909306}, {'name': 'Metas subscription service', 'weight': 0.07744459}, {'name': 'America', 'weight': 0.07631019}, {'name': 'creators', 'weight': 0.074268445}]",[{'name': 'Bank of America'}],"[{'data': 'Bank of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'BoFA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
572354b1a9da46acb924b8e6e79bd272,Bank of America Says Millions Will Pay For This Service Within a Year,2023-03-10T18:07:00+00:00,BAC,Financial Services,Banks - Diversified,"{'30_days_before': -0.1437233230012671, '5_days_before': -0.08414207972143894, '3_days_before': 0.005637317001037645, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0566335916820474, '1_days_after': -0.002407246523967066, '2_days_after': -0.0031567524548856696, '5_days_after': -0.03200814800614149, '30_days_after': -0.06485504365976791}",['https://www.thestreet.com/investing/bank-of-america-says-millions-will-pay-for-social-media-by-2024?puc=yahoo&cm_ven=YAHOO'],"[{'name': 'new revenue', 'weight': 0.12532733}, {'name': 'America analysts', 'weight': 0.121944}, {'name': 'CNBC', 'weight': 0.105763935}, {'name': 'researchers', 'weight': 0.088959344}, {'name': 'its paid subscription service', 'weight': 0.086613245}, {'name': 'businesses', 'weight': 0.08361979}, {'name': 'consumers', 'weight': 0.07909306}, {'name': 'Metas subscription service', 'weight': 0.07744459}, {'name': 'America', 'weight': 0.07631019}, {'name': 'creators', 'weight': 0.074268445}]",[{'name': 'Bank of America'}],"[{'data': 'Bank of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'BoFA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
