articleId,article,pubDate,ticker,sector,industry,netReturn,links,keywords,topics,entities,reprint,event,relationship,impact,event keyword,found_keywords,keywords_score
362e555ab8bc4fcdac05ae15cb50e508,Air Products (APD) Misses Earnings and Revenue Estimates in Q1,2023-02-02T14:46:02+00:00,APD,Basic Materials,Specialty Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.03601891419866121, '5_days_before': 0.01266905028835752, '3_days_before': 0.02563779127304089, '2_days_before': -0.001166807646599155, '1_days_before': -0.01787804774405466, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.08583384062446431, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': 0.012290416118885705, '30_days_after': 0.056203962447582856}","['https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=NUE&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2048396/air-products-apd-misses-earnings-and-revenue-estimates-in-q1?cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp/?ALERT=RPT_7BEST_YHOSYND&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_7BEST_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=APD&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=CMC&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=AEM&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396']","[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.13773471}, {'name': 'year over year', 'weight': 0.097393155}, {'name': 'adjusted earnings', 'weight': 0.09454535}, {'name': 'Earnings', 'weight': 0.08659425}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.08659425}, {'name': 'Zacks Consensus Estimate', 'weight': 0.08151315}, {'name': 'the past year', 'weight': 0.07563096}, {'name': 'current-year', 'weight': 0.07172466}, {'name': 'full-year fiscal 2023 adjusted earnings', 'weight': 0.07061815}, {'name': 'the prior-year quarter', 'weight': 0.069541514}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'Air Products', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'APD', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Jazan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Commercial Metals Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CMC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Nucor Corporation', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NUE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Agnico Eagle Mines Limited', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'AEM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Zacks Consensus Estimate', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Zacks Investment Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asia', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Americas', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Middle East', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'India', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Negative,Revenue Discussions,['sales increase'],8
362e555ab8bc4fcdac05ae15cb50e508,Air Products (APD) Misses Earnings and Revenue Estimates in Q1,2023-02-02T14:46:02+00:00,APD,Basic Materials,Specialty Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.03601891419866121, '5_days_before': 0.01266905028835752, '3_days_before': 0.02563779127304089, '2_days_before': -0.001166807646599155, '1_days_before': -0.01787804774405466, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.08583384062446431, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': 0.012290416118885705, '30_days_after': 0.056203962447582856}","['https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=NUE&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2048396/air-products-apd-misses-earnings-and-revenue-estimates-in-q1?cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp/?ALERT=RPT_7BEST_YHOSYND&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_7BEST_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=APD&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=CMC&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396', 'https://www.zacks.com/registration/pfp?ALERT=YAHOO_ZER&d_alert=ZER_CONF&t=AEM&ADID=SYND_YAHOO_TCK_ANALYSTBLOG_210&cid=CS-YAHOO-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2048396']","[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.13773471}, {'name': 'year over year', 'weight': 0.097393155}, {'name': 'adjusted earnings', 'weight': 0.09454535}, {'name': 'Earnings', 'weight': 0.08659425}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.08659425}, {'name': 'Zacks Consensus Estimate', 'weight': 0.08151315}, {'name': 'the past year', 'weight': 0.07563096}, {'name': 'current-year', 'weight': 0.07172466}, {'name': 'full-year fiscal 2023 adjusted earnings', 'weight': 0.07061815}, {'name': 'the prior-year quarter', 'weight': 0.069541514}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'Air Products', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'APD', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Jazan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Commercial Metals Company', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CMC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Nucor Corporation', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NUE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Agnico Eagle Mines Limited', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'AEM', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Zacks Consensus Estimate', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Zacks Investment Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asia', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Americas', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Middle East', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'India', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Negative,Margin/Profitability Discussions,['bottom line'],8
548e9e0e2e184b44801c80838373f17b,Natural gas company to increase capacity by nearly 20% with investment at Seaport Manatee,2023-07-31T17:59:00+00:00,APD,Basic Materials,Specialty Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.01936345859416888, '5_days_before': 0.01408097143786613, '3_days_before': 0.006261513857534817, '2_days_before': 0.006261513857534817, '1_days_before': 0.004792800917015505, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.006898173767682647, '1_days_after': -0.05591793661298594, '2_days_after': -0.041911524326363025, '5_days_after': -0.04127655673195818, '30_days_after': -0.004870617574463276}",['https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-poised-regain-crown-worlds-top-lng-exporter-2023-01-04/'],"[{'name': 'Air Products', 'weight': 0.09881315}, {'name': 'Seaport Manatee', 'weight': 0.08975091}, {'name': 'prefabricated plant modules', 'weight': 0.086570926}, {'name': 'Natural gas company', 'weight': 0.08151645}, {'name': 'unrivaled liquefaction process technology', 'weight': 0.07806128}, {'name': 'equipment', 'weight': 0.07584575}, {'name': 'January', 'weight': 0.072764896}, {'name': 'total worldwide LNG production', 'weight': 0.07171829}, {'name': 'skids', 'weight': 0.070798375}, {'name': 'its LNG equipment manufacturing facility', 'weight': 0.06613176}]","[{'name': 'Tampa'}, {'name': 'ESG'}, {'name': 'Florida'}]","[{'data': 'Seaport Manatee', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Air Products', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'APD', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Reuters', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lehigh Valley', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pennsylvania', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Florida', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Largo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Australia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'John Palamara', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'afternoon', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Industry Competitiveness,Causal,Positive,,[],0
3e5d37a7c33f415eae45bc57766c7f16,"Gulf of Mexico ""dead zone"" smaller than expected, still covers more than 3,000 square miles",2023-08-02T21:14:16.966000+00:00,CF,Basic Materials,Agricultural Inputs,"{'30_days_before': 0.14510857549124023, '5_days_before': -0.007140395311712067, '3_days_before': -0.008609108252231379, '2_days_before': -0.014757000807888887, '1_days_before': 0.006088438273694652, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.009739721070342489, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': 0.021014537779560416, '30_days_after': -0.028509200534730827}","['https://www.epa.gov/ms-htf/hypoxia-task-force-nutrient-reduction-strategies', 'https://edms.deq.louisiana.gov/app/doc/view?doc=13839122', 'https://www.epa.gov/ms-htf/gulf-hypoxia-program#:~:text=The%20Bipartisan%20Infrastructure%20Law%20provides%20a%20total%20of%20%2460%20million,per%20year%20for%20five%20years.', 'https://journalism.missouri.edu/2021/07/1-4-million-grant-to-missouri-school-of-journalism-helps-create-network-of-journalists-focused-on-mississippi-river-basin/', 'https://forms.gle/e4ggZEG4nLFcehcDA', 'https://www.columbiamissourian.com/priceofplenty/profit/farmers-navigate-the-tricky-terrain-of-profit-versus-planet/article_1328e4a6-f8fb-11ed-abeb-e35d4c3f7067.html', 'https://www.columbiamissourian.com/priceofplenty/elements/fixed-on-nitrogen-fundamental-to-life-and-a-key-ingredient-in-fertilizer-nitrogen-can-also/article_de7a0f7e-f34f-11ed-84d8-f320fda7a7a6.html', 'https://www.columbiamissourian.com/priceofplenty/landscape/a-lifetime-of-research-links-gulf-of-mexico-dead-zone-to-midwest-fertilizer-runoff/article_1d216dd2-f9bb-11ed-bba0-5b8d35cc1eae.html', 'https://oembed-dnr.mo.gov/document-search/missouri-nutrient-loss-reduction-strategy-2022-update', 'https://environmentalintegrity.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Refinery-water-pollution-report-EMBARGOED-until-1.26.23.pdf', 'http://www.reportforamerica.org/', 'https://www.columbiamissourian.com/priceofplenty/profit/nitrogen-fertilizer-releases-greenhouse-gases-throughout-its-life-cycle/article_eab95196-fbfb-11ed-ad01-df827203aab7.html', 'https://coastalscience.noaa.gov/news/price-of-shrimp-affected-by-gulf-of-mexico-dead-zone/', 'https://www.epa.gov/ms-htf', 'https://www.cfindustries.com/who-we-are/locations/donaldsonville', 'http://www.agwaterdesk.org/', 'https://healthygulf.org/press_releases/coalition-sues-epa-over-water-pollution/', 'https://www.noaa.gov/news-release/noaa-and-partners-announce-below-average-dead-zone-measured-in-gulf-of-mexico']","[{'name': 'nitrogen pollution', 'weight': 0.076493815}, {'name': 'more nitrogen pollution', 'weight': 0.07629341}, {'name': 'total nitrogen loads', 'weight': 0.07365734}, {'name': 'Mississippi River', 'weight': 0.07181782}, {'name': 'water pollution limits', 'weight': 0.07035298}, {'name': 'Nitrogen fertilizer', 'weight': 0.07022385}, {'name': 'nutrient pollution', 'weight': 0.06889202}, {'name': 'phosphorus loads', 'weight': 0.06802072}, {'name': 'excess nutrient pollution', 'weight': 0.0672705}, {'name': 'nitrogen products', 'weight': 0.063713945}]",[],"[{'data': 'Gulf of Mexico', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'the Mississippi River', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Atchafalaya Rivers', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Midwest', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'NOAA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Mississippi River/Gulf of Mexico', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Force', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Louisiana State University', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'LUMCON', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Environmental Protection Agency', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Agriculture', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EPA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Environmental Integrity Project', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ExxonMobil Baton Rouge Refinery', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CF Industries', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Air Products', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Mississippi River Basin Ag & Water Desk', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Report for America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Texas', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Florida', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Louisiana', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Iowa', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Donaldsonville', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'La.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lori Sprague', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nancy Rabalais', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mike Naig', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matt Rota', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Clean Water Act', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Gulf Hypoxia Action Plan', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
7a614122c07d4d82b721462daefeb8f4,"Nasdaq slips, Dow ekes out 10th day of gains: Stock market news today",2023-07-21T20:02:51+00:00,JNJ,Healthcare,Drug Manufacturers - General,"{'30_days_before': 0.028462587223160307, '5_days_before': 0.06761556541005853, '3_days_before': 0.010425266341691941, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.001195340742496498, '1_days_after': 0.0020697585114042294, '2_days_after': 0.014120271355799963, '5_days_after': 0.008889879562717695, '30_days_after': -0.0004955162508599731}","['https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/stock-market-news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EGSPC?p=%5EGSPC&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/key-statistics?fr=sycsrp_catchall', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/NFLX', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-says-the-worst-is-over-for-wall-street-111457107.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-sinks-as-tesla-netflix-plunge-dow-gains-for-9th-day-stock-market-news-today-200246194.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-are-seeing-a-resilient-us-consumer-194625188.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/MSFT?p=MSFT', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/TSLA', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=%5EDJI&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://yahoo.mydashboard.oath.com/guc-redirect?app=sellPersonalInformation&bucket=pd_2&lang=en-US']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.09647519}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.087602094}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.076254204}, {'name': '10th day', 'weight': 0.065489165}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.065111406}, {'name': 'Nasdaq', 'weight': 0.06436326}, {'name': 'Big Tech results', 'weight': 0.062891416}, {'name': 'season', 'weight': 0.061343305}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'NASDAQ'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NFLX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
7a614122c07d4d82b721462daefeb8f4,"Nasdaq slips, Dow ekes out 10th day of gains: Stock market news today",2023-07-21T20:02:51+00:00,TSLA,Consumer Cyclical,Auto Manufacturers,"{'30_days_before': 0.013328070260359093, '5_days_before': -0.11594626426016008, '3_days_before': -0.011278848990041945, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.030732436873092572, '1_days_after': -0.003350263304877643, '2_days_after': -0.02949595440799535, '5_days_after': 0.0011390029651288103, '30_days_after': -0.09099042048255856}","['https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/stock-market-news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EGSPC?p=%5EGSPC&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/key-statistics?fr=sycsrp_catchall', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/NFLX', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-says-the-worst-is-over-for-wall-street-111457107.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-sinks-as-tesla-netflix-plunge-dow-gains-for-9th-day-stock-market-news-today-200246194.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-are-seeing-a-resilient-us-consumer-194625188.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/MSFT?p=MSFT', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/TSLA', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=%5EDJI&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://yahoo.mydashboard.oath.com/guc-redirect?app=sellPersonalInformation&bucket=pd_2&lang=en-US']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.09647519}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.087602094}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.076254204}, {'name': '10th day', 'weight': 0.065489165}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.065111406}, {'name': 'Nasdaq', 'weight': 0.06436326}, {'name': 'Big Tech results', 'weight': 0.062891416}, {'name': 'season', 'weight': 0.061343305}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'NASDAQ'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NFLX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Negative,,[],0
7a614122c07d4d82b721462daefeb8f4,"Nasdaq slips, Dow ekes out 10th day of gains: Stock market news today",2023-07-21T20:02:51+00:00,NDAQ,Financial Services,Financial Data & Stock Exchanges,"{'30_days_before': 0.021555194668541278, '5_days_before': -0.015398134366129135, '3_days_before': 0.021848741175917397, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.002670712964576216, '1_days_after': -0.0027817121281872303, '2_days_after': -0.009085623247050534, '5_days_after': -0.014590702701303915, '30_days_after': 0.06652245664036649}","['https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/stock-market-news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EGSPC?p=%5EGSPC&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/key-statistics?fr=sycsrp_catchall', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/NFLX', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-says-the-worst-is-over-for-wall-street-111457107.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-sinks-as-tesla-netflix-plunge-dow-gains-for-9th-day-stock-market-news-today-200246194.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-are-seeing-a-resilient-us-consumer-194625188.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/MSFT?p=MSFT', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/TSLA', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=%5EDJI&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://yahoo.mydashboard.oath.com/guc-redirect?app=sellPersonalInformation&bucket=pd_2&lang=en-US']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.09647519}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.087602094}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.076254204}, {'name': '10th day', 'weight': 0.065489165}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.065111406}, {'name': 'Nasdaq', 'weight': 0.06436326}, {'name': 'Big Tech results', 'weight': 0.062891416}, {'name': 'season', 'weight': 0.061343305}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'NASDAQ'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NFLX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
7a614122c07d4d82b721462daefeb8f4,"Nasdaq slips, Dow ekes out 10th day of gains: Stock market news today",2023-07-21T20:02:51+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.032905008472480235, '5_days_before': -0.0010366255634348676, '3_days_before': -0.0003240945218980773, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.013459243325553483, '1_days_after': 0.0042691705322470686, '2_days_after': 0.03387898410377743, '5_days_after': 0.03378946024577889, '30_days_after': 0.04297229283490667}","['https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/stock-market-news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EGSPC?p=%5EGSPC&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/key-statistics?fr=sycsrp_catchall', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/NFLX', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-says-the-worst-is-over-for-wall-street-111457107.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-sinks-as-tesla-netflix-plunge-dow-gains-for-9th-day-stock-market-news-today-200246194.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-are-seeing-a-resilient-us-consumer-194625188.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/MSFT?p=MSFT', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/TSLA', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=%5EDJI&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://yahoo.mydashboard.oath.com/guc-redirect?app=sellPersonalInformation&bucket=pd_2&lang=en-US']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.09647519}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.087602094}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.076254204}, {'name': '10th day', 'weight': 0.065489165}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.065111406}, {'name': 'Nasdaq', 'weight': 0.06436326}, {'name': 'Big Tech results', 'weight': 0.062891416}, {'name': 'season', 'weight': 0.061343305}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'NASDAQ'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NFLX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
7a614122c07d4d82b721462daefeb8f4,"Nasdaq slips, Dow ekes out 10th day of gains: Stock market news today",2023-07-21T20:02:51+00:00,NFLX,Communication Services,Entertainment,"{'30_days_before': 0.00820718616219751, '5_days_before': -0.1019787801947124, '3_days_before': -0.023002557150982206, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0019990775796390192, '1_days_after': -0.011605137759117201, '2_days_after': -0.02739330042615351, '5_days_after': -0.007722908259004124, '30_days_after': -0.00671174765117033}","['https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/stock-market-news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EGSPC?p=%5EGSPC&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/key-statistics?fr=sycsrp_catchall', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/NFLX', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-says-the-worst-is-over-for-wall-street-111457107.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-sinks-as-tesla-netflix-plunge-dow-gains-for-9th-day-stock-market-news-today-200246194.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-are-seeing-a-resilient-us-consumer-194625188.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/MSFT?p=MSFT', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/TSLA', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=%5EDJI&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://yahoo.mydashboard.oath.com/guc-redirect?app=sellPersonalInformation&bucket=pd_2&lang=en-US']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.09647519}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.087602094}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.076254204}, {'name': '10th day', 'weight': 0.065489165}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.065111406}, {'name': 'Nasdaq', 'weight': 0.06436326}, {'name': 'Big Tech results', 'weight': 0.062891416}, {'name': 'season', 'weight': 0.061343305}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'NASDAQ'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NFLX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Negative,,[],0
7a614122c07d4d82b721462daefeb8f4,"Nasdaq slips, Dow ekes out 10th day of gains: Stock market news today",2023-07-21T20:02:51+00:00,MSFT,Technology,Software - Infrastructure,"{'30_days_before': 0.02611779880608389, '5_days_before': -0.04608655464038647, '3_days_before': -0.009261307131956276, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.00013613595337491624, '1_days_after': -0.03748217054843117, '2_days_after': -0.05114509187787708, '5_days_after': -0.03916178891470312, '30_days_after': -0.04457214436113355}","['https://finance.yahoo.com/topic/stock-market-news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EGSPC?p=%5EGSPC&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EIXIC/key-statistics?fr=sycsrp_catchall', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/NFLX', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-says-the-worst-is-over-for-wall-street-111457107.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-sinks-as-tesla-netflix-plunge-dow-gains-for-9th-day-stock-market-news-today-200246194.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-banks-are-seeing-a-resilient-us-consumer-194625188.html', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/MSFT?p=MSFT', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/TSLA', 'https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=%5EDJI&.tsrc=fin-srch', 'https://yahoo.mydashboard.oath.com/guc-redirect?app=sellPersonalInformation&bucket=pd_2&lang=en-US']","[{'name': 'Thursday', 'weight': 0.09647519}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.087602094}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.08357449}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.076254204}, {'name': '10th day', 'weight': 0.065489165}, {'name': 'Yahoo Finance', 'weight': 0.065111406}, {'name': 'Nasdaq', 'weight': 0.06436326}, {'name': 'Big Tech results', 'weight': 0.062891416}, {'name': 'season', 'weight': 0.061343305}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'NASDAQ'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NFLX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yahoo Finance', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
8910d52d717549d7864e9ac54efc9d79,Stock futures are little changed after Dow registers longest rally since 2017: Live updates,2023-07-20T22:02:01+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.02700961172928229, '5_days_before': 0.0024566510717118906, '3_days_before': 0.004708045673180283, '2_days_before': -0.0010366255634348676, '1_days_before': 0.01111137873396828, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0003240945218980773, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.013459243325553483, '5_days_after': 0.03539076455696999, '30_days_after': 0.05121778542570987}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/19/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TSLA/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/KNX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/JNJ/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/NFLX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CSX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/']","[{'name': 'Wall Street analysts', 'weight': 0.12306414}, {'name': 'Johnson', 'weight': 0.11795403}, {'name': 'FactSet data', 'weight': 0.11767196}, {'name': 'Wall Street', 'weight': 0.099093355}, {'name': 'AXS Investments', 'weight': 0.086827084}, {'name': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'weight': 0.0834061}, {'name': 'FactSet', 'weight': 0.07984348}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.07768334}, {'name': 'extended trading', 'weight': 0.070826575}, {'name': 'Greg Bassuk', 'weight': 0.06755589}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CSX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Knight-Swift', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FactSet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AXS Investments', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wall Street', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Greg Bassuk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
8910d52d717549d7864e9ac54efc9d79,Stock futures are little changed after Dow registers longest rally since 2017: Live updates,2023-07-20T22:02:01+00:00,CSX,Industrials,Railroads,"{'30_days_before': 0.02955395273460082, '5_days_before': 0.0023789274297749685, '3_days_before': 0.007632714053789513, '2_days_before': -0.003543087439604964, '1_days_before': 0.00409424951672821, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.037405113088222586, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.0021856184429192016, '5_days_after': 0.017324072381920796, '30_days_after': -0.02380682820490565}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/19/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TSLA/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/KNX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/JNJ/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/NFLX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CSX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/']","[{'name': 'Wall Street analysts', 'weight': 0.12306414}, {'name': 'Johnson', 'weight': 0.11795403}, {'name': 'FactSet data', 'weight': 0.11767196}, {'name': 'Wall Street', 'weight': 0.099093355}, {'name': 'AXS Investments', 'weight': 0.086827084}, {'name': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'weight': 0.0834061}, {'name': 'FactSet', 'weight': 0.07984348}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.07768334}, {'name': 'extended trading', 'weight': 0.070826575}, {'name': 'Greg Bassuk', 'weight': 0.06755589}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CSX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Knight-Swift', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FactSet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AXS Investments', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wall Street', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Greg Bassuk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
8910d52d717549d7864e9ac54efc9d79,Stock futures are little changed after Dow registers longest rally since 2017: Live updates,2023-07-20T22:02:01+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.02700961172928229, '5_days_before': 0.0024566510717118906, '3_days_before': 0.004708045673180283, '2_days_before': -0.0010366255634348676, '1_days_before': 0.01111137873396828, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0003240945218980773, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.013459243325553483, '5_days_after': 0.03539076455696999, '30_days_after': 0.05121778542570987}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/19/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TSLA/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/KNX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/JNJ/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/NFLX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CSX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/']","[{'name': 'Wall Street analysts', 'weight': 0.12306414}, {'name': 'Johnson', 'weight': 0.11795403}, {'name': 'FactSet data', 'weight': 0.11767196}, {'name': 'Wall Street', 'weight': 0.099093355}, {'name': 'AXS Investments', 'weight': 0.086827084}, {'name': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'weight': 0.0834061}, {'name': 'FactSet', 'weight': 0.07984348}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.07768334}, {'name': 'extended trading', 'weight': 0.070826575}, {'name': 'Greg Bassuk', 'weight': 0.06755589}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CSX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Knight-Swift', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FactSet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AXS Investments', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wall Street', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Greg Bassuk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
8910d52d717549d7864e9ac54efc9d79,Stock futures are little changed after Dow registers longest rally since 2017: Live updates,2023-07-20T22:02:01+00:00,CSX,Industrials,Railroads,"{'30_days_before': 0.02955395273460082, '5_days_before': 0.0023789274297749685, '3_days_before': 0.007632714053789513, '2_days_before': -0.003543087439604964, '1_days_before': 0.00409424951672821, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.037405113088222586, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.0021856184429192016, '5_days_after': 0.017324072381920796, '30_days_after': -0.02380682820490565}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/19/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TSLA/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/KNX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/JNJ/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/NFLX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CSX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/']","[{'name': 'Wall Street analysts', 'weight': 0.12306414}, {'name': 'Johnson', 'weight': 0.11795403}, {'name': 'FactSet data', 'weight': 0.11767196}, {'name': 'Wall Street', 'weight': 0.099093355}, {'name': 'AXS Investments', 'weight': 0.086827084}, {'name': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'weight': 0.0834061}, {'name': 'FactSet', 'weight': 0.07984348}, {'name': 'earnings', 'weight': 0.07768334}, {'name': 'extended trading', 'weight': 0.070826575}, {'name': 'Greg Bassuk', 'weight': 0.06755589}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CSX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Knight-Swift', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FactSet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Johnson & Johnson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AXS Investments', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wall Street', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Greg Bassuk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Margin/Profitability Discussions,Causal,Negative,,[],0
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.09958930282139478, '5_days_before': -0.02287212095650837, '3_days_before': -0.023895953803117487, '2_days_before': -0.026854118242251368, '1_days_before': -0.016584386384100758, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.003665203891579205, '1_days_after': 0.002988250116647495, '2_days_after': 0.002988250116647495, '5_days_after': 0.014233766052250796, '30_days_after': -0.011067915060307243}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Neutral,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,WMT,Consumer Defensive,Discount Stores,"{'30_days_before': 0.009281167340198015, '5_days_before': -0.020229713590159237, '3_days_before': -0.021493486296146114, '2_days_before': -0.024451650735279995, '1_days_before': -0.007449130945823779, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.013559925740316725, '1_days_after': -0.00885321537346817, '2_days_after': -0.00885321537346817, '5_days_after': -0.008363627856540878, '30_days_after': -0.023586021561985415}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Negative,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,GOOGL,Communication Services,Internet Content & Information,"{'30_days_before': 0.09442512920671287, '5_days_before': 0.026804275586937876, '3_days_before': 0.01701986153178736, '2_days_before': 0.01406169709265348, '1_days_before': 0.032126597144323865, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0007621122591137119, '1_days_after': 0.0008759445441511859, '2_days_after': 0.0008759445441511859, '5_days_after': 0.010300365291845415, '30_days_after': -0.04469115401237289}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,TGT,Consumer Defensive,Discount Stores,"{'30_days_before': -0.022110393206596024, '5_days_before': -0.004065673772265743, '3_days_before': -0.00011055555270789164, '2_days_before': -0.003068719991841773, '1_days_before': -0.00979896449021167, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.013920112708279753, '1_days_after': -0.010877419957580736, '2_days_after': -0.010877419957580736, '5_days_after': -0.033032518442265846, '30_days_after': -0.18250837652598617}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,NVDA,Technology,Semiconductors,"{'30_days_before': 0.08844213136805412, '5_days_before': 0.02380320995578178, '3_days_before': 0.030804510374056848, '2_days_before': 0.027846345934922967, '1_days_before': 0.01535768930187209, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.021142399141840906, '1_days_after': -0.011623150723127806, '2_days_after': -0.011623150723127806, '5_days_after': -0.018753313150114304, '30_days_after': 0.29743550518739026}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,TJX,Consumer Cyclical,Apparel Retail,"{'30_days_before': 0.014349515727160922, '5_days_before': 0.003633019889607181, '3_days_before': -0.009748075232988263, '2_days_before': -0.012706239672122144, '1_days_before': -0.006619216172012665, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.002558148760994472, '1_days_after': 0.002455129312901483, '2_days_after': 0.002455129312901483, '5_days_after': -0.009956280948995477, '30_days_after': -0.025285897440844973}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
45c58315c4e74161a861870ace67c1c8,CNBC Daily Open: Inflation weighed on consumer spending,2023-05-17T06:30:01+00:00,MSFT,Technology,Software - Infrastructure,"{'30_days_before': 0.08616052822005016, '5_days_before': 0.0068397398372507245, '3_days_before': 0.008965333816448595, '2_days_before': 0.006007169377314714, '1_days_before': 0.013745412123600476, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0024393909647733025, '1_days_after': 0.0008808947084302243, '2_days_after': 0.0008808947084302243, '5_days_after': 0.002263905353663165, '30_days_after': 0.02436199145218021}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/homebuilder-sentiment-may-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/sign-up-for-cnbc-newsletters/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/retail-sales-april-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/home-depot-hd-earnings-q1-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/16/what-home-depots-poor-outlook-means-for-the-stock-market-and-economy.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/10/cpi-inflation-april-2023.html']","[{'name': 'sales', 'weight': 0.0797492}, {'name': 'retail sales', 'weight': 0.077219985}, {'name': 'consumer spending', 'weight': 0.07508743}, {'name': 'consumer demand', 'weight': 0.06966763}, {'name': 'markets', 'weight': 0.06853576}, {'name': 'persistent inflation', 'weight': 0.06842588}, {'name': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'weight': 0.06733908}, {'name': 'this fiscal year', 'weight': 0.062375195}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.060283966}]","[{'name': 'Inflation'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'CNBC Daily Open', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'S&P', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TJX', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Robert Hum', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walton', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Cox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'each morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Revenue Discussions,Causal,Positive,Revenue Discussions,"['revenue expectations', 'sales report']",14
1159a1bb13cd4fd5b7719446f670ef33,Stock futures are flat with all eyes on key inflation report,2023-01-11T18:04:14-04:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.11930012792413902, '5_days_before': 0.046528561055674045, '3_days_before': 0.047296193600937175, '2_days_before': 0.034628243698116234, '1_days_before': 0.006807089090018481, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.012909236979529615, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': 0.0, '5_days_after': -0.013794948718538591, '30_days_after': -0.0034202618070036106}","['https://www.bls.gov/charts/consumer-price-index/consumer-price-index-by-category-line-chart.htm', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/11/cpi-inflation-is-expected-to-have-declined-in-december.html']","[{'name': 'Fed rate hikes', 'weight': 0.10078958}, {'name': 'price pressures', 'weight': 0.099406615}, {'name': 'tamer prices', 'weight': 0.09687277}, {'name': 'interest rates', 'weight': 0.0926117}, {'name': 'chief equity strategist', 'weight': 0.07914791}, {'name': 'Dow Jones', 'weight': 0.07878008}, {'name': 'key inflation report', 'weight': 0.07753691}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072155654}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07215517}, {'name': 'Jeff Buchbinder', 'weight': 0.068074696}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Inflation'}]","[{'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""the Federal Reserve's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Dow Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'overnight', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeff Buchbinder', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
a0a57c4da1874c11ac11d21a9e46d2d5,Dow to pay $457K to settle fraud suit regarding Minnesota highway work,2023-09-05T16:11:01.144000+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.002135307991463664, '5_days_before': -0.00858065446633971, '3_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '2_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '1_days_before': -0.015700965474997663, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.01988907477918611, '1_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '2_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '5_days_after': -0.01110483254949135, '30_days_after': -0.03856427330812873}",['https://www.startribune.com/the-drive-mndot-has-a-flaky-problem-with-the-mendota-bridge/494079991/'],"[{'name': 'Minnesota highway work', 'weight': 0.10607478}, {'name': 'False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.10040593}, {'name': 'Minnesota', 'weight': 0.09831275}, {'name': 'enamel paint products', 'weight': 0.095486894}, {'name': 'numerous road construction projects', 'weight': 0.08993681}, {'name': 'road construction projects', 'weight': 0.089844055}, {'name': 'enamel paint', 'weight': 0.08639919}, {'name': 'the Minnesota False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.07757255}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical', 'weight': 0.07669212}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical Co.', 'weight': 0.07662846}]","[{'name': 'Corruption'}, {'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Fraud'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Minnesota'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Poly-Carb Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'the Minnesota Department of Transportation', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'The Office of Inspector General', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MnDOT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'DuPont', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Olin Corp.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Minnesota', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South Carolina', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'False Claims Act', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Andrew Luger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Mendota Bridge', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
a0a57c4da1874c11ac11d21a9e46d2d5,Dow to pay $457K to settle fraud suit regarding Minnesota highway work,2023-09-05T16:11:01.144000+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.002135307991463664, '5_days_before': -0.00858065446633971, '3_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '2_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '1_days_before': -0.015700965474997663, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.01988907477918611, '1_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '2_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '5_days_after': -0.01110483254949135, '30_days_after': -0.03856427330812873}",['https://www.startribune.com/the-drive-mndot-has-a-flaky-problem-with-the-mendota-bridge/494079991/'],"[{'name': 'Minnesota highway work', 'weight': 0.10607478}, {'name': 'False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.10040593}, {'name': 'Minnesota', 'weight': 0.09831275}, {'name': 'enamel paint products', 'weight': 0.095486894}, {'name': 'numerous road construction projects', 'weight': 0.08993681}, {'name': 'road construction projects', 'weight': 0.089844055}, {'name': 'enamel paint', 'weight': 0.08639919}, {'name': 'the Minnesota False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.07757255}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical', 'weight': 0.07669212}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical Co.', 'weight': 0.07662846}]","[{'name': 'Corruption'}, {'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Fraud'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Minnesota'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Poly-Carb Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'the Minnesota Department of Transportation', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'The Office of Inspector General', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MnDOT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'DuPont', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Olin Corp.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Minnesota', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South Carolina', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'False Claims Act', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Andrew Luger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Mendota Bridge', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Defaults,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
a0a57c4da1874c11ac11d21a9e46d2d5,Dow to pay $457K to settle fraud suit regarding Minnesota highway work,2023-09-05T16:11:01.144000+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.002135307991463664, '5_days_before': -0.00858065446633971, '3_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '2_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '1_days_before': -0.015700965474997663, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.01988907477918611, '1_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '2_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '5_days_after': -0.01110483254949135, '30_days_after': -0.03856427330812873}",['https://www.startribune.com/the-drive-mndot-has-a-flaky-problem-with-the-mendota-bridge/494079991/'],"[{'name': 'Minnesota highway work', 'weight': 0.10607478}, {'name': 'False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.10040593}, {'name': 'Minnesota', 'weight': 0.09831275}, {'name': 'enamel paint products', 'weight': 0.095486894}, {'name': 'numerous road construction projects', 'weight': 0.08993681}, {'name': 'road construction projects', 'weight': 0.089844055}, {'name': 'enamel paint', 'weight': 0.08639919}, {'name': 'the Minnesota False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.07757255}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical', 'weight': 0.07669212}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical Co.', 'weight': 0.07662846}]","[{'name': 'Corruption'}, {'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Fraud'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Minnesota'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Poly-Carb Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'the Minnesota Department of Transportation', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'The Office of Inspector General', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MnDOT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'DuPont', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Olin Corp.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Minnesota', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South Carolina', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'False Claims Act', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Andrew Luger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Mendota Bridge', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,Mergers and Acquisitions,['merger'],7
a0a57c4da1874c11ac11d21a9e46d2d5,Dow to pay $457K to settle fraud suit regarding Minnesota highway work,2023-09-05T16:11:01.144000+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.002135307991463664, '5_days_before': -0.00858065446633971, '3_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '2_days_before': -0.01989514306250373, '1_days_before': -0.015700965474997663, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.01988907477918611, '1_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '2_days_after': -0.00863547787056207, '5_days_after': -0.01110483254949135, '30_days_after': -0.03856427330812873}",['https://www.startribune.com/the-drive-mndot-has-a-flaky-problem-with-the-mendota-bridge/494079991/'],"[{'name': 'Minnesota highway work', 'weight': 0.10607478}, {'name': 'False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.10040593}, {'name': 'Minnesota', 'weight': 0.09831275}, {'name': 'enamel paint products', 'weight': 0.095486894}, {'name': 'numerous road construction projects', 'weight': 0.08993681}, {'name': 'road construction projects', 'weight': 0.089844055}, {'name': 'enamel paint', 'weight': 0.08639919}, {'name': 'the Minnesota False Claims Act', 'weight': 0.07757255}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical', 'weight': 0.07669212}, {'name': 'Dow Chemical Co.', 'weight': 0.07662846}]","[{'name': 'Corruption'}, {'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Fraud'}, {'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Minnesota'}]","[{'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Poly-Carb Inc.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'the Minnesota Department of Transportation', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'The Office of Inspector General', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MnDOT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'DuPont', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Olin Corp.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Minnesota', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Michigan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Missouri', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South Carolina', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'False Claims Act', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Andrew Luger', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Mendota Bridge', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Mergers and Acquisitions,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,Mergers and Acquisitions,['merger'],7
c6b5f0b528284d9aa362ad6a65883cc8,"Stock futures are flat as traders look ahead to key inflation data, Fed meeting: Live updates",2023-06-11T22:01:53+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.0030513455319176597, '5_days_before': -0.012350783261548925, '3_days_before': -0.02085248404340534, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.008161576604926113, '1_days_after': -0.00702931510942606, '2_days_after': -0.00660929309242464, '5_days_after': -0.00891174727633759, '30_days_after': -0.01214420255283355}","['https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/08/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/']","[{'name': 'Fed meeting', 'weight': 0.1079502}, {'name': 'key inflation data', 'weight': 0.083417684}, {'name': 'Stock futures', 'weight': 0.08297729}, {'name': 'Closing Bell', 'weight': 0.08223028}, {'name': 'U.S. stock futures', 'weight': 0.079068586}, {'name': 'Federal Open Market Committee', 'weight': 0.077751935}, {'name': 'easing inflation', 'weight': 0.07123378}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.07036673}, {'name': 'Tom Lee', 'weight': 0.07026461}, {'name': 'the Federal Open Market Committee meeting', 'weight': 0.06794077}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Inflation'}]","[{'data': 'Fed', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fundstrat', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Federal Open Market Committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tom Lee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Closing Bell', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
2046cc36e2914160bf9581f655b52386,"Asian shares, oil advance on strong China factory data",2023-03-01T05:42:17+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.005153354859051884, '5_days_before': 0.022975853459008544, '3_days_before': 0.001926622732479455, '2_days_before': -0.0011463818346875154, '1_days_before': 0.0067208269658146635, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.019061019254300926, '1_days_after': -0.01820096831047391, '2_days_after': -0.01820096831047391, '5_days_after': -0.04643538293986493, '30_days_after': -0.09408367238574888}","['https://apnews.com/article/john-lee-hong-kong-business-health-pandemics-aacd0517f62f2b55291f96c8af5552cc', 'https://apnews.com/article/student-loan-forgiveness-supreme-court-hearing-2128da75fc27ff3bcc0c3804ebd98aa7', 'https://apnews.com/article/inflation-federal-reserve-system-financial-markets-off-the-charts-business-21ec8f876fee58758760cec8d050405b', 'https://apnews.com/article/climate-change-lithium-recycling-energy-mining-d68bfa6e7bf1586ded72229df29692b9', 'https://apnews.com/article/student-loan-forgiveness-supreme-court-payments-51ef087355f045260c37ae6fc698b38d', 'https://apnews.com/article/china-economy-manufacturing-caixin-pmi-5f64cb790de697b21130ce0f6ce56418', 'https://apnews.com/article/consumer-confidence-economy-spending-conference-board-63ffed65dbb378ba1293e245e10584bd', 'https://apnews.com/hub/business', 'https://apnews.com/article/economy-inflation-interest-rates-jobs-recession-f218111d29793783338e3ff6ec040da2']","[{'name': 'June last year', 'weight': 0.07473266}, {'name': 'more losses', 'weight': 0.07347743}, {'name': 'more volatility', 'weight': 0.06854843}, {'name': 'retail stocks', 'weight': 0.061719816}, {'name': 'Hong Kong Stock Exchange', 'weight': 0.06165517}, {'name': 'global growth', 'weight': 0.061303772}, {'name': 'High rates', 'weight': 0.060764197}, {'name': 'Tuesday', 'weight': 0.060196117}, {'name': 'upcoming earnings reports', 'weight': 0.057715897}, {'name': 'stringent anti-virus restrictions', 'weight': 0.056134056}]","[{'name': 'Asian'}, {'name': 'China'}]","[{'data': 'Asian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'South Korean', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Hong Kong', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'TOKYO', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Australia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Chicago', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hong Kong Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Caixin', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China Federation of Logistics & Purchasing', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Communist Party', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Hang Seng', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ally', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brent', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Louise Delmotte', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'John Lee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Overby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
2046cc36e2914160bf9581f655b52386,"Asian shares, oil advance on strong China factory data",2023-03-01T05:42:17+00:00,TGT,Consumer Defensive,Discount Stores,"{'30_days_before': 0.01917925912586893, '5_days_before': 0.028664513907792788, '3_days_before': 0.009223698659033275, '2_days_before': 0.0061506940918663044, '1_days_before': 0.013167167246328604, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.03147649778512207, '1_days_after': -0.015786029071807706, '2_days_after': -0.015786029071807706, '5_days_after': -0.02006271897946932, '30_days_after': -0.03400790106695151}","['https://apnews.com/article/john-lee-hong-kong-business-health-pandemics-aacd0517f62f2b55291f96c8af5552cc', 'https://apnews.com/article/student-loan-forgiveness-supreme-court-hearing-2128da75fc27ff3bcc0c3804ebd98aa7', 'https://apnews.com/article/inflation-federal-reserve-system-financial-markets-off-the-charts-business-21ec8f876fee58758760cec8d050405b', 'https://apnews.com/article/climate-change-lithium-recycling-energy-mining-d68bfa6e7bf1586ded72229df29692b9', 'https://apnews.com/article/student-loan-forgiveness-supreme-court-payments-51ef087355f045260c37ae6fc698b38d', 'https://apnews.com/article/china-economy-manufacturing-caixin-pmi-5f64cb790de697b21130ce0f6ce56418', 'https://apnews.com/article/consumer-confidence-economy-spending-conference-board-63ffed65dbb378ba1293e245e10584bd', 'https://apnews.com/hub/business', 'https://apnews.com/article/economy-inflation-interest-rates-jobs-recession-f218111d29793783338e3ff6ec040da2']","[{'name': 'June last year', 'weight': 0.07473266}, {'name': 'more losses', 'weight': 0.07347743}, {'name': 'more volatility', 'weight': 0.06854843}, {'name': 'retail stocks', 'weight': 0.061719816}, {'name': 'Hong Kong Stock Exchange', 'weight': 0.06165517}, {'name': 'global growth', 'weight': 0.061303772}, {'name': 'High rates', 'weight': 0.060764197}, {'name': 'Tuesday', 'weight': 0.060196117}, {'name': 'upcoming earnings reports', 'weight': 0.057715897}, {'name': 'stringent anti-virus restrictions', 'weight': 0.056134056}]","[{'name': 'Asian'}, {'name': 'China'}]","[{'data': 'Asian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'South Korean', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Hong Kong', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'TOKYO', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Australia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Chicago', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hong Kong Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Caixin', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China Federation of Logistics & Purchasing', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Communist Party', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Hang Seng', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Target', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ally', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brent', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Louise Delmotte', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'John Lee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Overby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
883fd0905dfc4f45bde4e14a9089112a,Stock futures are flat to start the week,2023-05-07T22:01:17+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': -0.0045736144925454525, '5_days_before': 0.018712823053930405, '3_days_before': 0.001202967523323828, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.005230769848820316, '1_days_after': -0.008582978225999627, '2_days_after': -0.027560816438963687, '5_days_after': -0.02653207509127864, '30_days_after': -0.045141185289171326}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/jobs-report-april-2023-job-growth-totals-25300-in-april.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/OXY/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TPR/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.B/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-brka-q1-earnings-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-wont-take-full-control-of-occidental-petroleum.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/regional-bank-stocks-rebound-on-friday-but-still-headed-for-steep-losses-on-the-week.html', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/PYPL/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting-live-updates.html']","[{'name': 'higher borrowing costs', 'weight': 0.076417625}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.074465275}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072650895}, {'name': 'chief global strategist', 'weight': 0.06515646}, {'name': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'weight': 0.06403109}, {'name': 'Quincy Krosby', 'weight': 0.060792223}, {'name': 'commercial real estate', 'weight': 0.060367744}, {'name': 'volatile regional bank stocks', 'weight': 0.059719235}, {'name': 'morning trading', 'weight': 0.059060417}, {'name': 'billionaire investor Warren Buffett', 'weight': 0.053082403}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Berkshire Hathaway 's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CME', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FedWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tapestry', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omaha', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nebraska', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warren Buffett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Quincy Krosby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
883fd0905dfc4f45bde4e14a9089112a,Stock futures are flat to start the week,2023-05-07T22:01:17+00:00,OXY,Energy,Oil & Gas E&P,"{'30_days_before': -0.03727794634344861, '5_days_before': 0.017824425225123175, '3_days_before': 0.01542647675101061, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.028957577980838756, '1_days_after': -0.04027090420516766, '2_days_after': -0.0202493131842183, '5_days_after': -0.015947815135921584, '30_days_after': -0.02666041700068522}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/jobs-report-april-2023-job-growth-totals-25300-in-april.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/OXY/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TPR/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.B/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-brka-q1-earnings-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-wont-take-full-control-of-occidental-petroleum.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/regional-bank-stocks-rebound-on-friday-but-still-headed-for-steep-losses-on-the-week.html', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/PYPL/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting-live-updates.html']","[{'name': 'higher borrowing costs', 'weight': 0.076417625}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.074465275}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072650895}, {'name': 'chief global strategist', 'weight': 0.06515646}, {'name': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'weight': 0.06403109}, {'name': 'Quincy Krosby', 'weight': 0.060792223}, {'name': 'commercial real estate', 'weight': 0.060367744}, {'name': 'volatile regional bank stocks', 'weight': 0.059719235}, {'name': 'morning trading', 'weight': 0.059060417}, {'name': 'billionaire investor Warren Buffett', 'weight': 0.053082403}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Berkshire Hathaway 's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CME', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FedWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tapestry', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omaha', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nebraska', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warren Buffett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Quincy Krosby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
883fd0905dfc4f45bde4e14a9089112a,Stock futures are flat to start the week,2023-05-07T22:01:17+00:00,PYPL,Financial Services,Credit Services,"{'30_days_before': 0.00013343298229240297, '5_days_before': 0.04421472021181261, '3_days_before': 0.02553031433313624, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.006884077997188376, '1_days_after': -0.042796654102644216, '2_days_after': -0.028953749387824246, '5_days_after': -0.06514772296282079, '30_days_after': -0.06768973657587274}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/jobs-report-april-2023-job-growth-totals-25300-in-april.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/OXY/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TPR/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.B/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-brka-q1-earnings-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-wont-take-full-control-of-occidental-petroleum.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/regional-bank-stocks-rebound-on-friday-but-still-headed-for-steep-losses-on-the-week.html', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/PYPL/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting-live-updates.html']","[{'name': 'higher borrowing costs', 'weight': 0.076417625}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.074465275}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072650895}, {'name': 'chief global strategist', 'weight': 0.06515646}, {'name': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'weight': 0.06403109}, {'name': 'Quincy Krosby', 'weight': 0.060792223}, {'name': 'commercial real estate', 'weight': 0.060367744}, {'name': 'volatile regional bank stocks', 'weight': 0.059719235}, {'name': 'morning trading', 'weight': 0.059060417}, {'name': 'billionaire investor Warren Buffett', 'weight': 0.053082403}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Berkshire Hathaway 's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CME', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FedWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tapestry', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omaha', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nebraska', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warren Buffett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Quincy Krosby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
883fd0905dfc4f45bde4e14a9089112a,Stock futures are flat to start the week,2023-05-07T22:01:17+00:00,CME,Financial Services,Financial Data & Stock Exchanges,"{'30_days_before': -0.051102033227756194, '5_days_before': 0.004842407414547667, '3_days_before': -0.011950358608412204, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.0025729270757750555, '1_days_after': -0.0008008909635879302, '2_days_after': -0.009008381580980274, '5_days_after': 0.0005411345476304952, '30_days_after': -0.031895625973929365}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/jobs-report-april-2023-job-growth-totals-25300-in-april.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/OXY/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TPR/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.B/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-brka-q1-earnings-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-wont-take-full-control-of-occidental-petroleum.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/regional-bank-stocks-rebound-on-friday-but-still-headed-for-steep-losses-on-the-week.html', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/PYPL/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting-live-updates.html']","[{'name': 'higher borrowing costs', 'weight': 0.076417625}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.074465275}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072650895}, {'name': 'chief global strategist', 'weight': 0.06515646}, {'name': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'weight': 0.06403109}, {'name': 'Quincy Krosby', 'weight': 0.060792223}, {'name': 'commercial real estate', 'weight': 0.060367744}, {'name': 'volatile regional bank stocks', 'weight': 0.059719235}, {'name': 'morning trading', 'weight': 0.059060417}, {'name': 'billionaire investor Warren Buffett', 'weight': 0.053082403}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Berkshire Hathaway 's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CME', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FedWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tapestry', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omaha', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nebraska', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warren Buffett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Quincy Krosby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
883fd0905dfc4f45bde4e14a9089112a,Stock futures are flat to start the week,2023-05-07T22:01:17+00:00,TPR,Consumer Cyclical,Luxury Goods,"{'30_days_before': -0.02890591525049746, '5_days_before': -0.013363415381960397, '3_days_before': 0.0051659635287930605, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.013795941935569989, '1_days_after': -0.03451811350594758, '2_days_after': 0.04736384263268811, '5_days_after': 0.07428457591546289, '30_days_after': 0.07632008907708276}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/jobs-report-april-2023-job-growth-totals-25300-in-april.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/OXY/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TPR/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.B/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-brka-q1-earnings-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-wont-take-full-control-of-occidental-petroleum.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/regional-bank-stocks-rebound-on-friday-but-still-headed-for-steep-losses-on-the-week.html', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/PYPL/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting-live-updates.html']","[{'name': 'higher borrowing costs', 'weight': 0.076417625}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.074465275}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072650895}, {'name': 'chief global strategist', 'weight': 0.06515646}, {'name': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'weight': 0.06403109}, {'name': 'Quincy Krosby', 'weight': 0.060792223}, {'name': 'commercial real estate', 'weight': 0.060367744}, {'name': 'volatile regional bank stocks', 'weight': 0.059719235}, {'name': 'morning trading', 'weight': 0.059060417}, {'name': 'billionaire investor Warren Buffett', 'weight': 0.053082403}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Berkshire Hathaway 's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CME', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FedWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tapestry', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omaha', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nebraska', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warren Buffett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Quincy Krosby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
883fd0905dfc4f45bde4e14a9089112a,Stock futures are flat to start the week,2023-05-07T22:01:17+00:00,DIS,Communication Services,Entertainment,"{'30_days_before': 0.0055016171023720695, '5_days_before': 0.006203053459706842, '3_days_before': 0.013028587281672888, '2_days_before': 0.0, '1_days_before': 0.0, 'day_of_article_movement': 0.023921108440799754, '1_days_after': -0.014662075418148457, '2_days_after': -0.09937402368171899, '5_days_after': -0.1009179839887222, '30_days_after': -0.13686724973661146}","['https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/jobs-report-april-2023-job-growth-totals-25300-in-april.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/OXY/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TPR/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.B/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@ND.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@DJ.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-brka-q1-earnings-2023.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-wont-take-full-control-of-occidental-petroleum.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/regional-bank-stocks-rebound-on-friday-but-still-headed-for-steep-losses-on-the-week.html', 'https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/PYPL/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/@SP.1/', 'https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/06/berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting-live-updates.html']","[{'name': 'higher borrowing costs', 'weight': 0.076417625}, {'name': 'New York City', 'weight': 0.074465275}, {'name': 'LPL Financial', 'weight': 0.072650895}, {'name': 'chief global strategist', 'weight': 0.06515646}, {'name': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'weight': 0.06403109}, {'name': 'Quincy Krosby', 'weight': 0.060792223}, {'name': 'commercial real estate', 'weight': 0.060367744}, {'name': 'volatile regional bank stocks', 'weight': 0.059719235}, {'name': 'morning trading', 'weight': 0.059060417}, {'name': 'billionaire investor Warren Buffett', 'weight': 0.053082403}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'the New York Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NYSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': ""Berkshire Hathaway 's"", 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Occidental Petroleum', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LPL Financial', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CME', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FedWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tapestry', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'evening', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omaha', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nebraska', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warren Buffett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Quincy Krosby', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}]",False,Other,Causal,Positive,,[],0
e26b2e6e9ccb4db79e28febabb3c2c91,Second-round leaders shoot 61 in Dow Great Lakes Bay Invitational,2023-07-21T01:52:26.863000+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.02700961172928229, '5_days_before': 0.0024566510717118906, '3_days_before': 0.004708045673180283, '2_days_before': -0.0010366255634348676, '1_days_before': 0.01111137873396828, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0003240945218980773, '1_days_after': 0.0, '2_days_after': -0.013459243325553483, '5_days_after': 0.03539076455696999, '30_days_after': 0.05121778542570987}","['https://www.mlive.com/sports/saginaw-bay-city/2023/06/pettersen-qualifier-gives-amateurs-shot-at-dow-lpga-stop.html', 'https://www.mlive.com/sports/2023/07/2022-runners-up-lead-dow-great-lakes-bay-invitational-by-one-after-first-round.html', 'https://www.mlive.com/sports/saginaw-bay-city/2023/07/midlands-kimberly-dinh-added-to-lpga-dow-great-lakes-bay-field.html', 'https://www.lpga.com/tournaments/dow-great-lakes-bay-invitational/leaderboard']","[{'name': 'alternate shot', 'weight': 0.10168487}, {'name': 'Dow Great Lakes Bay Invitational', 'weight': 0.090592355}, {'name': 'Great Lakes Bay Invitational', 'weight': 0.084277324}, {'name': 'Midland Country Club', 'weight': 0.08329456}, {'name': 'birdies', 'weight': 0.07332532}, {'name': 'American Amelia Lewis', 'weight': 0.070597574}, {'name': 'such good holes', 'weight': 0.06709321}, {'name': 'American Emma Talley', 'weight': 0.06313898}, {'name': 'opposite holes', 'weight': 0.06268425}, {'name': 'the Dow Great Lakes Bay Invitational', 'weight': 0.06125161}]","[{'name': 'Dow Jones'}, {'name': 'Markets'}]","[{'data': 'Dow Great Lakes Bay Invitational', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Paula Reto', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Amelia Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Jodi Ewart Shadoff', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Emma Talley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Matilda Castren', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kelly', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Celine Boutier', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Yuka Saso', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Celine Borge', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Polly Mack', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly Dinh', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jasmine Ly', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lexi Thompson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Brooke Henderson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South Africa', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'England', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Finland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Midland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Canada', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Midland Country Club', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the LPGA Tour', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '2 1/2-hour', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the afternoon', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Non-Causal,Not Relevant,,[],0
349511214dea46a793abc84854260588,Stocks Waver Ahead of Powell Speech,2023-02-07T17:00:28+00:00,DOW,Basic Materials,Chemicals,"{'30_days_before': 0.10054950205815094, '5_days_before': 0.019695642716193507, '3_days_before': 0.008500008792638791, '2_days_before': 0.014640471810393185, '1_days_before': -0.005882955149226987, 'day_of_article_movement': -0.0004876085106978456, '1_days_after': 0.010329978178272858, '2_days_after': 0.010329978178272858, '5_days_after': -0.001875044283051519, '30_days_after': -0.022954493527473807}",['https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-02-07-2023/card/stocks-waver-ahead-of-powell-speech-S3zuAGTA83Fve5kvX6lE'],"[{'name': 'Powell Speech', 'weight': 0.1647982}, {'name': 'Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell', 'weight': 0.14880551}, {'name': 'Jerome Powell', 'weight': 0.14072728}, {'name': 'Powell', 'weight': 0.12062668}, {'name': 'Monday', 'weight': 0.10484867}, {'name': 'Major U.S. stock indexes', 'weight': 0.10282749}, {'name': 'Federal Reserve', 'weight': 0.0994647}, {'name': 'Stocks', 'weight': 0.08702008}, {'name': 'U.S. Treasury', 'weight': 0.07925028}, {'name': '0.1%', 'weight': 0.078417}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],"[{'data': 'Powell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'midday', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S. Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}]",False,Other,Causal,Neutral,,[],0
